♪ NA-NA-NA NA-NA-NA-NA NA-NA ♪
♪ NA-NA-NA NA NA-NA NA ♪
♪ YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ BEYOND COMPARE,
CAN'T HELP BUT STARE ♪
♪ SO FULL OF LIFE ♪
♪ INSPIRED,
LIKE A LONELY CHILD ♪
♪ YOU'RE MAGICAL ♪
♪ YOUR BLESSED STARE,
I APPRECIATE IT ♪
♪ YOU STOP THE CLOUDS ♪
♪ FROM CRYING INSIDE ♪
♪ BUT YOU DON'T SEE
WHO YOU ARE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU MEAN ♪
♪ I WISH YOU COULD SEE
YOURSELF THROUGH MY EYES ♪
♪ TRY, 'CAUSE I DON'T LOVE YOU
FOR YOU ♪
♪ OH, BABY,
WON'T YOU COME MY WAY? ♪
♪ YOUR BEAUTY'S TRUE ♪
♪ DON'T LISTEN
TO WHAT FOOLS MIGHT SAY ♪
♪ BEAUTIFUL YOU ♪
♪ OH, BABY,
I'M SO BLOWN AWAY ♪
♪ WITH EVERYTHING YOU DO ♪
♪ YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ NA-NA-NA NA NA-NA NA ♪
♪ NA-NA-NA NA-NA-NA-NA NA-NA ♪
♪ BEAUTIFUL YOU ♪
♪ OH, BABY,
WON'T YOU COME MY WAY? ♪
♪ YOUR BEAUTY'S TRUE ♪
♪ DON'T LISTEN
TO WHAT FOOLS MIGHT SAY ♪
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
HEY, JANE, IT'S KURT
FROM THE GYM.
BOY, I'M LOOKING FORWARD
TO OUR DATE TOMORROW.
I'LL SEE YOU IN THE PARK,
AND BRING SUNSCREEN.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
Jane: I CAN'T BELIEVE
NO ONE'S IN THE PARK TODAY.
WELL, PERHAPS THEY LISTENED
TO THE WEATHER REPORT.
[BOTH LAUGH]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHO CARES.
I'VE ACTUALLY ALWAYS
WANTED TO DO THIS.
[LAUGHS]
HOW LONG HAVE YOU LIVED
IN THE LOWER EAST SIDE?
6 YEARS.
WHY DO YOU SAY IT
LIKE THAT?
OH, 'CAUSE IT'S NOT
THE UPPER EAST SIDE.
WELL,
IF YOU'D HAVE MOVED,
I WOULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN TO SPEND
THE LAST YEAR AT THE GYM
TRYING TO WORK UP THE NERVE
TO ASK YOU OUT.
YOU WERE NOT.
WELL, OBVIOUSLY
I THOUGHT YOU WERE CUTE.
OH, WELL, THE WORK AT THE GYM
HAS REALLY PAID OFF.
OH, YEAH? YOU'VE BEEN
CHECKING OUT THE PIPES?
[BOTH LAUGH]
WOW, ARE YOU--
ARE YOU ALWAYS THAT FORWARD?
ACTUALLY,
I'M NEVER THAT FORWARD.
YOU HAVE, UM,
A STRANGE EFFECT ON ME.
YEAH, WELL, BE CAREFUL--
I MAY HAVE TO USE IT
TO MY ADVANTAGE.
HEY, YOU'VE BEEN DOING
ALL THE WORK. CAN I
GIVE YOU A BREAK?
NO, YOU JUST SIT THERE
AND LOOK PRETTY.
[LAUGHS]
I THINK IT'D BE
EASIER TO HELP.
NO, THIS ISN'T HARD.
THE LAST PERSON
I TOOK OUT HERE,
HER END OF THE BOAT
WAS PRACTICALLY UNDERWATER.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYIN'?
BIG GIRL.
[LAUGHS]
OH.
YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW
NO ONE LIKES TO HEAR IT
BUT, YOU KNOW, GIRLS GOT TO
TAKE CARE OF THEMSELVES.
GUYS ARE VISUAL--
YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE US
SOMETHING TO LOOK AT.
SURE.
DON'T WORRY--
YOU LOOK GREAT.
[LAUGHS]
EXCEPT FOR THAT BELLY SHIRT
YOU WEAR AT THE GYM.
BUT I ASSUMED
THAT YOU WEAR THAT
TO TURN GUYS OFF
SO THEY DON'T
BOTHER YOU, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
YEAH, I-I KNEW IT.
SEE, I KNOW
HOW GIRLS THINK--
IT'S A GIFT, REALLY.
WHOA!
[Echoing] NO!
WAH-HOO!
IT'S A GOOD THING
WE'RE GETTING ALONG SO GREAT--
IF THIS HAD HAPPENED
WITH THAT FAT CHICK,
I'D OF HAD TO
THROW MYSELF OVERBOARD.
THIS IS GOOD, THIS IS GOOD--
WE CAN GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
'CAUSE I KNOW HOW
YOU GIRLS LOVE TO TALK.
♪ TALK, TALK, TALK, TALK,
TALK, TALK, TALK ♪
TALK, TALK, TALK, TALK, TALK ♪
♪ DOO DOO-DOO DOO-DOO
TALK ♪
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BANGING]
[OPERA MUSIC PLAYS]
[WOMAN LAUGHS]
YOU HAVE NO NEW MESSAGES.
[BEEP]
Man: HA HA HA HA HA!
HA HA HA HA HA!
OH, IT'S JUST LIKE
MY COUSIN DANA
TO PULL A STUNT
LIKE THIS.
LIKE WHAT--
GET MARRIED?
I THINK IT'S NICE SHE'S
LETTING YOU BRING A GUEST.
NICE? IT'S NOT NICE--
IT'S MOCKING.
IT'S SAYING, "I'M BARELY OLDER
THAN BRITNEY SPEARS
"AND GETTING MARRIED
AT THE CARLTON
AND YOU HAVE NO ONE
WITH AN ACTUAL NAME
TO BRING TO MY WEDDING."
OK, WHAT IS THIS?
WE WERE PROMISED
MODERN NUDES.
IT'S A MAN AND A WOMAN
MAKING LOVE.
I SEE ROADKILL.
[LAUGHS]
AND BY THE WAY, "EW" FOR
THE PHRASE "MAKING LOVE."
WHO ARE YOU BRINGING
TO THE WEDDING?
I DON'T KNOW.
IF YOU HAVE A TUX
AND A FAKE MOUSTACHE,
YOU'RE IN THE RUNNING!
OOH! OR YOU CAN LET US
SET YOU UP!
YEAH, I WAS JUST
STRANDED AT SEA
WITH A GUY WHOSE
FAVORITE EVENT THIS YEAR
WAS THE LAUNCH
OF HOOTERS AIR.
MY DATING DAYS
ARE OVER.
WHAT DATING DAYS?
YOU HAD ONE DATE.
YEAH, AND THE LESSON
WE LEARNED
IS THAT IT WAS
TOO SOON.
HON, YOU AND MAX
BROKE UP A YEAR AGO.
OH! AND THE FORMULA SAYS
IT DOES TAKE HALF THE TIME
A COUPLE WAS TOGETHER
TO GET OVER THE BREAKUP.
SO CONSIDERING YOU WENT OUT
FOR 2 YEARS
AND BROKE UP
A YEAR AGO,
YOU SHOULD BE OUT THERE,
JANE, HAVING FUN.
"FUN" IS NOT HOW
I WOULD DESCRIBE BEING SET UP
WITH ALL THE OTHER LOSERS
WHO CAN'T GET DATES.
IT CAN'T BE THAT BAD.
OH, BUT IT IS.
YOU JUST DON'T REMEMBER
BECAUSE YOU'RE MARRIED,
AND YOU HAVE SERGE.
DO YOU WANT SERGE?
HE'S STARTING TO BUG ME.
THIS IS HOT!
IT'S PRACTICALLY
PORNOGRAPHY.
ALL RIGHT,
DON'T LET HER SET YOU UP.
WHERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
OK, UH,
ONE CRèME BRULéE.
THANK YOU.
ONE WHITE CHOCOLATE
CHEESECAKE.
ONE POWDERED
CHOCOLATE TRUFFLE.
AND NONFAT MILK
FOR THE COFFEE.
SO WHAT DO WE THINK, HUH?
DATE MATERIAL?
HE'S A WAITER!
HI, SNOB.
WELL,
JANE HAS STANDARDS.
NO, JANE
REALLY DOESN'T.
BUT SHE'S
STILL NOT DATING,
AND SHE'S DEFINITELY NOT
REFERRING TO HERSELF
IN THE THIRD PERSON
ANYMORE.
DID YOU HEAR ABOUT
NATASHA NUTLEY?
SHE WAS THE GIRL WHO BEAT YOU
FOR JUNIOR CLASS PRESIDENT
'CAUSE SHE WORE A HALTER TOP
FOR HER CAMPAIGN.
AND THE ONE WHO SQUASHED
ALL OF MY SELF-ESTEEM
WITH HER MERE EXISTENCE.
OUR BRILLIANT
EMPLOYERS AT BLUSH
HAVE DECIDED TO PUBLISH
HER TELL-ALL BIOGRAPHY.
"BLUSH --EVER ON THE EDGE
OF YESTERDAY'S NEWS."
I HATE TO ADMIT IT, BUT HER
STORY MAY BE THE ONE THING
THAT BRINGS BLUSH
BACK INTO THIS DECADE.
SO WHY DOES NATASHA NUTLEY
GET A BIOGRAPHY?
HEY!
ONE BITE.
THE GNAT WAS IN
A COUPLE OF SOAPS,
BUT HER BIG BREAK
WAS A SMALL PART AS A FEMBOT
IN AUSTIN POWERS.
YOU CALL HER
"THE GNAT"?
WELL, NOT
TO HER FACE.
ANYWAY, NOBODY WOULD HAVE
EVER KNOWN WHO SHE WAS
OUTSIDE OF OUR HOMETOWN,
BUT SHE DID HAVE A SECRET AFFAIR
WITH AN A-LIST ACTOR.
ONE OF PEOPLE'S
SEXIEST MEN ALIVE.
ANTONIO BANDERAS?!
I DON'T KNOW.
HUGH GRANT?!
I SAID I DON'T KNOW.
ROBERT REDFORD.
[Laughing] NO!
[LAUGHS]
HE'S, LIKE, A MILLION.
I'M TELLING YOU,
SHE CALLS HIM "THE ACTOR."
HE MADE HER SIGN A DOCUMENT.
AND IT SAYS IF SHE EVER
DISCUSSED HIM BY NAME,
HE COULD SUE HER
FOR EVERYTHING SHE'S GOT.
ASHTON KUTCHER?
STOP IT.
FINE.
I'VE HAD A KNOT
IN MY STOMACH ALL WEEK,
AND IT'S HARD TO SAY
IF IT'S BECAUSE OF THE GNAT
OR BECAUSE I'M ASKING REMKE
FOR A PROMOTION ON MONDAY
OR POSSIBLY BECAUSE I ATE
SOMETHING FROM MY FRIDGE.
[LAUGHS]
DAVID LETTERMAN!
THIS IS THE INITIAL LINE-EDIT
ON THE HASSELHOFF BOOK.
I NEED YOU TO MAKE A COPY
AND GIVE IT TO MAX.
AFTER MAX DOES HIS EDITS,
I NEED YOU TO COPY IT
AND GIVE IT TO REMKE.
AFTER REMKE'S DONE WITH IT,
WE WILL HAVE ACCOMPLISHED
WHAT IS KNOWN AS
"EDITING...
OUT OF SOMETHING."
YOU KNOW, IF YOU JUST
DID IT RIGHT ON YOUR OWN,
YOU WOULD SAVE THE REST OF US
A LOT OF WORK.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[RING]
JANE GRANT.
JANE, HI!
IT'S YOUR AUNT INA CALLING!
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE RAISED ME
SINCE I WAS A TEENAGER--
I THINK I'D RECOGNIZE
YOUR VOICE.
OH, HONEY, I-I'M JUST SO SORRY
TO BOTHER YOU AT WORK,
BUT I HAVE SOMETHING
VERY IMPORTANT TO TELL YOU.
IS EVERYTHING
ALL RIGHT?
YES, YES, YES.
IT'S JUST THAT
THE OTHER DAY
I WENT OUT TO SEE
MY DEAR FRIEND
EVELYN BURNS IN QUEENS.
ANYWAY, I HAVE HER HELPING ME
WITH DANA'S WEDDING.
WHILE I WAS THERE,
I MET THE NICEST YOUNG MAN.
HE WAS TAKING HIS TRASH
TO THE INCINERATOR.
I DON'T WANT
TO BE SET UP.
HONEY, HE'S
IN BUSINESS SCHOOL!
HIS NAME IS ETHAN MILES.
I DON'T WANT
TO BE SET UP.
HE'S A VERY GOOD-LOOKING
YOUNG MAN!
OH, REALLY?
[CHUCKLES] I KNEW
THAT WOULD GET YOU.
NO, I DON'T WANT
TO BE SET UP.
JANE, NOW YOU LISTEN TO ME,
ALL RIGHT?
YOU DON'T HAVE
A SIGNIFICANT OTHER
IN YOUR LIFE RIGHT NOW,
AND I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE
JUST A LITTLE EMBARRASSING
FOR YOU TO SHOW UP
AT DANA'S WEDDING ALONE.
NOW, I HAVE HEARD
THAT ETHAN IS ALSO SINGLE
AND HE'S NOT BUSY
THE DAY OF THE WEDDING.
HOW DID YOU HAPPEN
TO HEAR THAT?
I ASKED HIM!
WILLIAM WILL BE READY
TO SEE YOU
IN EXACTLY ONE MINUTE.
I'M SORRY, AUNT INA,
I HAVE TO GO.
BYE FOR NOW, HONEY.
OH, HEY, MAX.
THE BIG PROMOTION
TALK'S TODAY, RIGHT?
I'M ON MY WAY RIGHT NOW.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
I KNOW.
JUST BE CONFIDENT.
I AM CONFIDENT.
YOU'RE SHAKING.
I KNOW--
I'M EXCITED!
WELL, GOOD LUCK.
THANKS.
OH, AND DON'T DO THAT THING
WHERE YOU MAKE STATEMENTS
AS IF THEY'RE QUESTIONS.
OK, WELL, YOU'RE NOT
MY BOYFRIEND ANYMORE
SO YOU DON'T GET TO
BE THAT HONEST.
RIGHT.
THANKS.
OH, THERE YOU ARE, GRANT.
MORGAN, COFFEE!
I HAVE ANOTHER MEETING
IN 10 MINUTES!
[SIGHS]
LET'S GO, LET'S GO!
[LAUGHS]
UM, I WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT MY FUTURE
HERE AT BLUSH.
AS YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN HERE
FOR 6 YEARS NOW.
MAYBE YOU DON'T KNOW THAT
'CAUSE YOU PROBABLY HAVE
BETTER THINGS TO DO THAN
KEEP TRACK OF MY EMPLOYMENT.
ANYWAY, I WAS JUST THINKING
THAT DURING THIS TIME
I'VE DONE GOOD WORK,
AND I THOUGHT THAT IT
MIGHT BE APPROPRIATE FOR ME
TO MOVE INTO A POSITION
OF MORE RESPONSIBILITY.
MORGAN, WHERE'S
THAT PRESS RELEASE ON
THE NATASHA NUTLEY DEAL?
HERE YOU ARE.
[SIGHS]
WHO WROTE THIS?
UM, I DID?
ARE YOU ASKING ME
OR TELLING ME?
I'M TELLING YOU I DID.
IT'S GOOD.
REALLY?
UH, YES--THANK YOU.
I KNOW HOW MUCH
THIS PROJECT MEANS TO YOU.
GRANT--STOP TALKING.
SORRY.
I WANT YOU TO OVERSEE
THE NUTLEY MEMOIR.
WHAT?
YOU HAVE HISTORY
WITH HER.
YOU'LL GET HER TO GAB,
LIKE IN HIGH SCHOOL.
OH. [LAUGHS]
WE WEREN'T ACTUALLY--
TAKE HER TO LUNCH TOMORROW.
WHERE ARE YOU TAKING HER?
THE BISTRO?
ASKING
OR TELLING, GRANT.
TELLING--THE BISTRO.
AS YOU WELL KNOW,
THINGS HAVE BEEN ROCKY
AROUND HERE LATELY.
NATASHA NUTLEY
IS BIG FOR US.
DON'T SCREW IT UP.
RIGHT.
I EXPECT NOTHING LESS THAN
THE TIMES BEST-SELLER LIST.
THEN, MAYBE, WE'LL
TALK ABOUT A PROMOTION
TO ASSISTANT EDITOR.
ASSOCIATE EDITOR,
SIR. I'M ALREADY
THE ASSISTANT EDITOR?
MORGAN!
GET MAX IN HERE
TO DISCUSS WHERE WE ARE
ON THE JOHN TESH BOOK.
AND MORE COFFEE!
LET'S GO, LET'S GO!
YOU'RE STILL HERE?
NO.
OH, EXCUSE ME, COULD I--
COULD I PLEASE, UM--
WAITER!
JANE?
I THOUGHT
THAT WAS YOU!
DANA, HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
OH, I'M HAVING A LUNCH MEETING
WITH MY FABULOUS CATERER.
HE WAS ON THE TEAM
FOR IVANA'S THIRD WEDDING.
OH, WIDELY CONSIDERED
TO BE HER BEST.
YOU'RE NOT HAVING LUNCH ALONE,
ARE YOU? THAT'S SO AWKWARD.
NO, I'M NOT,
I'M ACTUALLY--
ALL RIGHT,
WELL, LET ME GO!
I JUST HAVE
A MILLION THINGS TO DO.
IF YOU EVER GET MARRIED,
YOU'LL SEE. [LAUGHS]
JANEY!
NATASHA!
OH--GOOD TO SEE
YOU AGAIN.
WOW, I JUST CAN'T
GET OVER IT!
JANEY GRANT.
I MEAN, WHO WOULD OF THOUGHT
WE'D BE WORKING TOGETHER?
CERTAINLY NOT ME.
AND YOU JUST LOOK ADORABLE!
WELL, YOU LOOK GREAT, TOO,
AS ALWAYS.
WELL, WE HAVE
A LOT TO COVER,
SO I THOUGHT
WE'D JUMP RIGHT IN.
UM, I WAS LOOKING OVER
YOUR PROPOSAL
AND I NOTICED YOU WENT WITH
A CHRONOLOGICAL STRUCTURE.
OH, JANEY, COME ON!
ALL BUSINESS?
WE HAVEN'T SEEN EACH OTHER
IN, LIKE, 10 YEARS!
I MEAN, I WAS SHOCKED
WHEN I HEARD MY EDITOR
WAS GONNA BE
LITTLE JANEY GRANT
FROM FOREST HILLS.
YOU KNOW,
I LIVE IN MANHATTAN NOW.
OH, REALLY? WHERE?
MY BOYFRIEND AND I HAVE A PLACE
ON THE UPPER WEST SIDE.
UPPER EAST SIDE.
FANCY!
WELL, ACTUALLY
IT'S MY BOYFRIEND'S PLACE.
I'M THERE ALL THE TIME.
H-HE'S A DOCTOR.
OOH!
OH, MY GOD!
NATASHA!
NATASHA NUTLEY!
DANA!
GET OUTTA HERE!
HI!
JANE--
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME
YOU WERE HAVING LUNCH
WITH NATASHA NUTLEY!
[Laughing]
YOU DIDN'T GIVE ME A CHANCE--
THE LAST TIME I SAW YOU,
YOU WERE BABYSITTING ME
AND I WAS BEGGING YOU TO LET ME
STAY UP AND WATCH MIAMI VICE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I'M A WRITER NOW--
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?--
AND JANEY'S HELPING ME.
DID JANE TELL YOU I'M GETTING
MARRIED AT THE CARLTON?
THE CARLTON?
I MANAGED TO SNAG
THE ONLY INTERNET MILLIONAIRE
WHO GOT OUT IN TIME
TO HOLD ONTO HIS CASH.
GOOD GIRL.
NOT THAT IT'S JUST ABOUT
THE MONEY, I MEAN.
HE'S ALSO GORGEOUS AND SWEET
AND FUNNY AND SENSITIVE,
BUT STILL A GUY'S GUY,
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, HE COULD GO OUT
AND PLAY FOOTBALL
AND THEN COME HOME
AND WRITE POETRY FOR ME.
OH, MY GOD! YOU HAVE TO COME
TO THE WEDDING! AUGUST 30th!
OH, THAT'LL BE
SO MUCH FUN!
I'LL GET TO MEET
YOUR NEW HUSBAND-TO-BE
AND JANEY'S BOYFRIEND
ALL IN THE SAME DAY!
BOYFRIEND?
WHAT BOYFRIEND?
OH, HE'S A DOCTOR.
REALLY? I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE SEEING SOMEONE.
YOU MUST'VE JUST MET.
HARDLY! THEY'RE PRACTICALLY
LIVING TOGETHER!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME!
AND I REALLY CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DIDN'T TELL MY MOTHER.
I DIDN'T WANT
TO JINX IT.
WELL, IT'S JUST WITH YOUR
SPOTTY DATING HISTORY,
I WOULD THINK IF YOU WERE
PRACTICALLY LIVING WITH A DOCTOR
YOU WOULD TELL
THE ENTIRE WORLD.
YOU KNOW,
I'M GOING TO HAVE THE T-SHIRTS
PRINTED UP LATER TODAY.
WELL, I GUESS IT DOESN'T MATTER
SINCE WE'LL ALL GET TO MEET
THE DOCTOR WHO YOU'RE
PRACTICALLY LIVING WITH
AT THE WEDDING.
THERE'S NO REASON YOU WOULDN'T
BRING HIM TO THE WEDDING, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
I WAS GONNA ASK YOU
IF YOU NEED ANY HELP,
BUT CLEARLY
YOU'VE DONE THIS BEFORE.
AND YET IT DOESN'T GET
ANY MORE FUN.
AW, COME ON--
WHO DOESN'T ENJOY
BEING FORCED TO BUY
GIFTS FOR COUPLES
THAT THEY WILL NEVER
END UP USING?
AH, CASE IN POINT.
AS A SINGLE PERSON,
I HAVE LIVED ALMOST 30 YEARS
BUT APPARENTLY WHEN YOU GET
MARRIED, ZESTING BECOMES
A BIG PART OF YOUR LIFE.
YEAH, AND IT'S
NOT JUST ZESTING.
IT'S TORCHING
CRèME BRULéE,
MAKING ICE CREAM,
GRILLING PANINI.
HOW IS IT
THAT MARRIED PEOPLE
DON'T WEIGH
A THOUSAND POUNDS?
AND THEN, OF COURSE, THERE'S
THE WHOLE WAFFLE IRON MYSTERY.
AND THE COUPLES
JUST KEEP REGISTERING.
YEAH, I'VE BEEN HERE A YEAR--
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
OH, A YEAR?
YOU DESERVE A MEDAL
OR...COUNSELING.
FORTUNATELY FOR ME
IT'S ONLY A TEMPORARY GIG.
DID YOU JUST SAY "GIG"?
YEAH--
I'M NOT PROUD OF IT.
CLEARLY JOB STRESS.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
THERE IS TROUBLE BREWING
OVER BY THE FONDUE POTS.
I BETTER GET OVER THERE
BEFORE THEY CANCEL THE WEDDING.
I'VE SEEN IT HAPPEN.
DID YOU FIND ANYTHING
FOR DANA AND LARRY?
OH, HARDLY.
I MEAN, WHAT DO YOU GET A GUY
THAT'S FUNNY BUT SERIOUS,
ATHLETIC BUT POETIC,
MASCULINE BUT FEMININE--
BOYFRIEND?
OF COURSE--THE ONE THING
THEY DON'T HAVE HERE.
LARRY CAN'T BE THAT PERFECT.
I'M SURE IF WE TRY WE'D FIND
SOMETHING WRONG WITH HIM.
[SIGHS] IT'S SO UNFAIR!
DANA'S, LIKE, 12 YEARS OLD.
HOW ARE WOMEN LIKE YOU
SUPPOSED TO COMPETE?
BRIGHT, TALENTED,
SMART WOMEN LIKE YOU.
ALL RIGHT, I-I DIDN'T THINK
I WAS GONNA SAY THIS,
BUT IN LIGHT OF THE WHOLE
"AND GUEST" SITUATION,
I MIGHT
ACTUALLY CONSIDER--
WHAT IS THAT?
JEFF TOLD SOME OF HIS CO-WORKERS
ABOUT YOU AT WORK,
BUT I PICKED OUT 3 THAT SEEM
LIKE REALLY GOOD CANDIDATES.
BUT YOU KNEW
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE SET UP.
HONEY,
YOU'RE DESPERATE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE HAVE KEVIN ADAMS,
SENIOR ACCOUNTANT.
GREAT EYES--ALL
THE ADMINS IN JEFF'S OFFICE
SALIVATE OVER HIM.
WELL, THEN,
I HOPE HE SHOWERS.
HANK CHILTON--GOOD-LOOKING,
ASSERTIVE, SUPER-SMART.
WAY BETTER
THAN "REGULAR SMART."
AND TIMOTHY ROMMELLY--
32, UPPER EAST SIDE DOCTOR.
DING DING DING--
I THINK WE HAVE A WINNER!
[LAUGHS]
I KNOW.
SO I GAVE THEM ALL
YOUR CELLPHONE NUMBER,
SO EXPECT THEIR CALLS.
BUT YOU KNOW I DON'T USE
MY CELLPHONE--IT'S FOR
EMERGENCIES ONLY.
JANE, DANA'S WEDDING'S
IN A MONTH. I'M SURE
THIS QUALIFIES.
[OPERA MUSIC PLAYS]
HI, JANE,
IT'S YOUR AUNT INA CALLING.
I JUST WANTED TO REMIND YOU
TO PICK UP YOUR BRIDESMAID'S
SHOES BEFORE THE WEDDING.
IT'LL BE HERE
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
AND YOU'LL WANT TIME
TO BREAK THEM IN.
SPEAKING OF THE WEDDING,
I HEARD WE'LL BE MEETING
YOUR BOYFRIEND THERE?
I DON'T REMEMBER
HEARING ABOUT A BOYFRIEND.
I'D ALWAYS ASSUMED
WE WERE CLOSE.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
WELL, IF IT DOESN'T WORK OUT,
ETHAN MILES WILL BE HAPPY
TO FILL IN.
BYE FOR NOW, HONEY.
HEY!
AMANDA SAYS WE'RE
ALLOWED TO SET YOU UP.
I JUST LEFT HER
10 MINUTES AGO.
HEY, WE'RE LIKE THE NATIONAL
GUARD--WE MOBILIZE QUICKLY.
[LAUGHS]
[COUPLE LAUGHING]
OPERA MAN'S
AT IT AGAIN?
YEAH, EVERY DAY--
EXCEPT DURING LENT,
WHEN IT'S TWICE A DAY.
I MADE A FEW CALLS
TO SEE IF ANYONE KNEW
ANYONE SINGLE.
OF COURSE, NO ONE DID.
SHOCK.
BUT THEN I REMEMBERED
THIS GUY IN MY YOGA CLASS.
OH, YOGA GUYS ARE GOOD.
OK, IT'S NOT HIM.
HE HAS THIS FRIEND,
GRANT, WHO'S REPORTED
TO BE NICE, FUNNY, AND CUTE,
BUT WHO HAS NO AFFINITIES
FOR BETTE, LIZA, OR CHER.
THE ONLY THING IS--
THERE'S ALWAYS A THING.
HE HAS A BREATHALYZER
IN HIS CAR.
EW.
HE HAD A COUPLE OF DUIs
A FEW YEARS BACK,
BUT IT'S NOT A HABIT,
HE FEELS UNBELIEVABLY
AWFUL ABOUT IT,
AND OBVIOUSLY
IT WON'T BE HAPPENING AGAIN.
I DON'T KNOW.
AT LEAST HE HAS A CAR.
[LAUGHS]
AND YOU'D ALWAYS
BE FREE TO DRINK
'CAUSE YOU'D HAVE
A SOBER RIDE HOME.
I GUESS.
AND THE WEDDING'S
IN A MONTH.
OK, WHY DOES EVERYONE
KEEP REMINDING ME OF THIS?
TOUGH LOVE.
FINE.
[LAUGHS]
WE'LL SET UP A DINNER PARTY--
YOU CAN CHECK HIM OUT.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE HIM,
THERE'S NO HARM DONE.
FAMOUS LAST WORDS.
OK, I HAVE TO GO.
I SLIPPED AN EXCEDRIN P.M.
INTO SERGE'S MEAT LOAF,
SO HE SHOULD BE OUT BY NOW.
OK, I HAVE NO IDEA
IF YOU'RE KIDDING.
[DOOR OPENS]
WE GOT SOME GOOD NEWS
THIS MORNING--
BLUSH IS MOVING FORWARD ON
A NEW PROJECT--A BIG ONE--
GOD KNOWS WE COULD USE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
ALL ABOUT OVERCOMING OBSTACLES
AND THE TRIUMPH
OF THE HUMAN SPIRIT--
A MEMOIR ENTITLED
THE SADDEST SWEATHOG.
WHICH SWEATHOG
WOULD THAT BE?
JUAN EPSTEIN,
OBVIOUSLY.
OR THE GUY
WITH THE ANNOYING LAUGH.
HORSHACK? HE'S NOT SAD--
HE'S A HOUSEHOLD NAME.
I GOTTA GO WITH
FREDDY "A BOOM BOOM" WASHINGTON.
YOU'RE RIGHT, MAX,
BOOM BOOM'S GOT IT.
OK, THE LAST PIECE OF BUSINESS
IS THE NUTLEY MEMOIR.
MARIE CLAIRE HAS AGREED
TO RUN AN EXCERPT
OF THE FIRST CHAPTER.
THAT'S FANTASTIC.
WHOA--THAT'S
NOT A LOT OF TIME.
WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
UM, YOU KNOW, JUST THAT WE HAVE
TO GET A LOT OF THINGS DONE,
AND WE WILL.
WHICH YOU WILL.
THIS IS YOUR PROJECT,
SO YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT'S GOT TO STAY ON NATASHA.
OH, NOT A PROBLEM.
NUTLEY'S NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE.
YOU NEED TO GUIDE HER.
WHATEVER SHE COMES UP WITH WILL
BE A DIRECT REFLECTION ON YOU.
NOT A PROBLEM--
AGAIN.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
SHE ABSOLUTELY HAS TO GET
THE CHAPTER TO YOU
A WEEK FROM FRIDAY.
THAT'S A HARD DEADLINE--
IT CANNOT BE LATE.
OTHERWISE WE CAN
FORGET MARIE CLAIRE,
AND WE'RE NOT GOING
TO FORGET MARIE CLAIRE.
ACTUALLY, WE HAVE A MEETING
AFTER WE FINISH HERE,
SO I EXPECT TO GET
A LOT OF WORK DONE.
[CLEARS THROAT]
DO YOU NEED TO ANSWER YOUR BAG?
WHAT?
OH, RIGHT!
OH, GOD, EXCUSE ME.
I AM SO SORRY.
IT'S PROBABLY NATASHA,
READY TO WORK.
HELLO?
HI, JANE? THIS IS KEVIN ADAMS.
I WORK WITH JEFF.
OH, HI, KEVIN.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU WANTED TO
MEET ME FOR DRINKS TOMORROW--
SAY O'REAGAN'S
AROUND 7:00?
YEAH, UM, O'REAGAN'S
SOUNDS GREAT.
UH, HOW WILL
I RECOGNIZE YOU?
I'LL HAVE ON
A GRAY SHIRT AND JEANS.
GREAT, I'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW FOR DRINKS. BYE.
THE DATE PHONE--
WHO WAS IT?
GUY NUMBER ONE--
KEVIN ADAMS,
SENIOR ACCOUNTANT.
GREAT EYES,
COVERED IN DROOL.
WE'RE GONNA MEET
FOR DRINKS TOMORROW.
[SIGHS]
WHAT?
THE DRINKS DATE
IS SO NON-COMMITTAL.
IT'S LIKE YOU ONLY GET
THE DINNER ADD-ON
IF YOU PERFORM WELL.
WELL, IT'S A GOOD THING I'VE
BEEN PRACTICING MY TRICKS.
I CAN ACTUALLY GET THE BALL
TO BALANCE ON MY NOSE NOW.
I AM SO EXCITED
TO BE WORKING ON THIS.
I MEAN, WHO WOULD OF
EVER THOUGHT,
ME, AN AUTHOR?
WELL, YOU'VE GOT
AN INTERESTING STORY TO TELL.
AND I WILL BE SO RELIEVED
WHEN I AM FINALLY ABLE
TO TELL MY SIDE
OF THE STORY.
WELL, ALONG
THOSE LINES,
WE JUST FOUND OUT
THAT MARIE CLAIRE
WOULD LIKE TO DO AN EXCERPT
ON YOUR FIRST CHAPTER.
OH, MY GOD!
MARIE CLAIRE IS THE BEST!
WELL, THE ONLY
THING, THOUGH, IS
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO FINISH A CHAPTER
PRETTY QUICKLY--
THEY NEED IT
NEXT FRIDAY.
OOH, A DEADLINE--
THAT'S SO WRITER-Y.
WELL, YES, AND IT'S ALSO
VERY IMPORTANT--NEXT FRIDAY.
GOT IT!
UH, OK.
YOU KNOW, UM, THIS IS WHAT
WRITERS CALL A DISTRACTION.
OH, I'M SORRY!
COULD WE TAKE
A LITTLE BREAK, PLEASE?
SURE.
[LAUGHS]
SO, WHAT'S
THIS AD FOR?
UM, SOME HIGH-TECH
WATER DRINK.
OH, WELL, MAYBE THIS
WILL BE A SPRINGBOARD
TO ONE OF THOSE
MILK MOUSTACHE CAMPAIGNS.
YOU THINK?
YEAH!
[BOTH LAUGH]
SO, UH, UM--
OH, NO, HONEY!
SEE, YOU HAVE TO SCRAPE
THE BAGEL GUTS OUT--
IT SHOULD BE A SHELL.
[LAUGHS]
OK, HERE'S
WHAT I WAS THINKING--
WE'LL START TODAY
PUTTING TOGETHER
A REALLY SUPER-DETAILED OUTLINE
OF THE FIRST CHAPTER
SO WHEN YOU ACTUALLY
START THE WRITING,
EVERYTHING WILL
PRACTICALLY BE DONE.
OH, WELL,
YOU CAN STOP WORRYING
ABOUT THE FIRST CHAPTER
BECAUSE AFTER OUR LUNCH
I WAS SO INSPIRED
THAT I JUST WENT AHEAD
AND I STARTED WRITING.
I WROTE AND WROTE
ALL NIGHT LONG.
YOU DID?
SO,
CAN I READ YOU
WHAT I HAVE SO FAR?
YES.
"I WAS IN
THE MIDDLE OF...
"ONE OF THE MOST FAMOUS ACTORS
IN SHOW BUSINESS
WHEN HE HANDED ME
A LEGAL DOCUMENT TO SIGN."
THAT'S IT!
WELL, I FIGURED THE FIRST
SENTENCE WAS THE MOST IMPORTANT,
SO I WANTED TO SPEND
A LONG TIME ON IT.
OK, WELL,
THE REST OF THE CHAPTER'S
GONNA BE A LOT OF WORK.
YOU KNOW, FRIDAY'S ONLY
A COUPLE OF DAYS AWAY.
WAIT--THIS FRIDAY?
YES.
OH, I THOUGHT YOU MEANT
NEXT FRIDAY.
NO, NO--
I SAID THIS FRIDAY.
WOW, WELL,
I GUESS WE'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO JUMP RIGHT IN THEN.
OH, GOOD, OK!
NATASHA, WE'RE
READY FOR YOU.
OOPS!
BREAK'S OVER.
OK, I'M ONLY GOOD
FOR ANOTHER HOUR.
GRAY SHIRT AND JEANS.
ARE YOU JANE?
[GASPS]
YEAH.
YOU WALKED RIGHT BY ME.
I JUST THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA
WEAR A GRAY SHIRT AND JEANS.
OH, WELL.
OH, I SEE WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE--
THE OLD GETAWAY OUTFIT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU KNOW,
JUST THAT IF YOU SAW ME
AND YOU DIDN'T WANT
THE DATE TO HAPPEN,
YOU COULD KIND OF
[SWISH] ESCAPE.
SURE.
UH, I'LL HAVE A BEER.
2 PINTS.
OH, AND 2 WATERS,
PLEASE.
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME
THE WATER.
I JUST THOUGHT OF IT.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO
BE JUDGED BY YOU
BECAUSE I DIDN'T THINK
OF THE WATER THING.
NO JUDGING--
I SWEAR.
I'M SORRY, I'M PROBABLY
A LITTLE SENSITIVE.
MY EX, KAREN, GOD--
I COULD NEVER DO ANYTHING
RIGHT WITH HER.
I WAS ALWAYS
SECOND-GUESSING.
SO YOU MUST'VE BEEN RELIEVED
WHEN YOU DECIDED TO MOVE ON.
YEAH, NOT REALLY--
SHE DUMPED ME.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO?
EXCEPT GO OUT AND TRY
TO MEET NEW PEOPLE...
WHO ARE PROBABLY GOING TO DO
THE SAME THING TO YOU.
TO BETTER SITUATIONS.
YOU KNOW,
IF IT'S ANY CONSOLATION,
I JUST WENT THROUGH A BREAKUP
MYSELF NOT TOO LONG AGO,
AND I KNOW HOW PAINFUL
IT CAN BE.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE ARE TRYING
TO BE HELPFUL,
AND THEY'RE JUST
PUSHING YOU INTO DATES
WHEN REALLY ALL YOU NEED
TO DO IS JUST KINDA
WORK THROUGH THINGS YOURSELF
AT YOUR OWN PACE.
RIGHT.
I'M SORRY--
ARE YOU SIGNALING
TO SOMEONE?
WHAT?
IT FEELS LIKE YOU'RE HAVING SOME
KIND OF SECRET CONVERSATION.
UH, YEAH.
THAT'S--THAT'S
MY FRIEND RICK.
WELL, S-SHOULD
YOU GO SAY HI?
OH, NO,
WE CAME TOGETHER.
EVER SINCE KAREN,
I DON'T REALLY TRUST MYSELF
TO MAKE GOOD CHOICES.
I NEEDED
A SECOND OPINION.
OK, WELL, THEN,
WHY DON'T WE JUST PRETEND
HE'S NOT THERE THEN?
YEAH, HE DOESN'T THINK
THIS IS GOING ANYWHERE.
EXCUSE ME?!
HE SENSES YOU MIGHT BE
A LITTLE NEEDY
AND NOT REALLY
OVER YOUR EX.
WELL, YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
GO AHEAD AND GO THEN.
NO HARD FEELINGS.
ACTUALLY, I'D KIND OF LIKE
TO HAVE A BEER WITH RICK.
MAYBE YOU COULD LEAVE.
RIGHT.
HE'S ALL YOURS.
Jane:
AW, POOR JOANNA CRUM.
Eloise: WHY?
SHE COULDN'T GET HER SCHLUB
OF A FIANCé TO POSE
IN THE ANNOUNCEMENT PHOTO
WITH HER.
YEAH, THAT MARRIAGE
IS GONNA LAST.
SHE'S 26.
AND WHAT--OLD MAID?
GOTTA TAKE WHAT SHE CAN GET?
NO! IT'S JUST,
AS PEOPLE GET OLDER,
THEY'RE MORE WILLING
TO OVERLOOK THINGS
IN THE INTEREST
OF FINDING SOMEONE.
CODE FOR "LOWER
YOUR STANDARDS."
NO, IT'S NOT LOWERING--
IT'S DEFINITELY REASSESSING
YOUR PRIORITIES.
YOU KNOW, FOR INSTANCE,
I ALWAYS THOUGHT I'D END UP
WITH SOMEONE ATHLETIC.
AND AT 20,
I CAN HOLD OUT FOR THAT.
COMING UP ON 30, YEAH,
I'M OK WITH THE FACT THAT ALL
JEFF PLAYS IS THE CLARINET.
HEY, SHOULDN'T YOU BE READING
THE GNAT'S FIRST CHAPTER?
I SHOULD, EXCEPT SHE HASN'T
GIVEN IT TO ME YET.
SHE MISSED HER
FAKE DEADLINE.
LOOK HOW SMART I WAS
TO ASSUME SHE'D FLAKE.
WELL, I HAVE TILL NEXT WEEK
TO GET IT FROM HER, SO--
AH, SHE PROBABLY GOT COCKY
BECAUSE WHAT YOU SAID
SHE DID WAS GOOD.
NICE WORD CHOICE.
BLIND DATE HOTLINE!
HELLO?
HI, JANE?
THIS IS HANK CHILTON--
JEFF'S FRIEND.
OH, HI, HANK.
OH, GOOD-LOOKING,
ASSERTIVE, SUPER-SMART.
I WAS, UH, WONDERING
IF YOU WERE FREE FOR DINNER
ON SATURDAY.
I AM FREE FOR DINNER
NO! YOU NEVER ADMIT
YOU'RE FREE ON SATURDAY!
GREAT. WHY DON'T WE MEET
AT 9:00 AT NATE'S?
I'LL BE THE TALL ONE
WITH DARK HAIR, GREEN EYES,
AND A REALLY
NERVOUS EXPRESSION.
[LAUGHS] OK,
I'LL SEE YOU THEN.
THAT GIVES US A WEEK
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW WE'RE GONNA
PACKAGE YOU.
WE STILL HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
THE DINNER PARTY, TOO.
OH, RIGHT--
YOGA GUY'S FRIEND!
I'M THINKING SHE SHOULD WEAR
SOMETHING FLOWY, YOU KNOW?
MAYBE YOU CAN READ UP
ON HOLISTIC MEDICINE.
HERE'S A CRAZY THOUGHT,
BUT WHAT IF I JUST GO AS I AM?
Both:
THE WEDDING'S IN 3 WEEKS.
EXCUSE ME--
I DIDN'T MEAN TO EAVESDROP,
BUT WHEN YOU TALK ON YOUR
CELLPHONE IN A PUBLIC PLACE,
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET.
WILL YOU PEOPLE FIND
A NEW SCAPEGOAT?
GET THE SMOKERS
BACK IN HERE.
I WAS KIDDING!
I KNEW SHE WAS
SELF-CONSCIOUS ABOUT IT,
SO I WENT FOR THE EASY JOKE.
WHICH, NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT
IT, WASN'T SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
LET ME START AGAIN--
I'M GARY.
SHE'S JANE.
DOESN'T MATTER WHO WE ARE.
OH, WELL, I'M A COORDINATOR
FOR CITY-CARE.
WE DO ALL SORTS OF
VOLUNTEER WORK, AND--
JANE LOVES
VOLUNTEER WORK.
WELL, WE'RE STARTING UP
THIS NEW MONTHLY ACTIVITY
FOR SINGLES--
KIND OF A SELF-SERVING
PUBLIC SERVICE.
I DON'T KNOW
YOUR SITUATION--
SHE'S SINGLE.
YES, APPARENTLY I LEFT
MY SCARLET "S" AT HOME.
WELL, THIS SATURDAY
WE'RE CLEANING UP THE PARK--
EXCEPT FOR THE REALLY
DISGUSTING THINGS,
BECAUSE WE'RE ONLY VOLUNTEERS.
ANYWAY, IT WOULD BE GREAT
TO SEE YOU.
SHE'LL BE THERE.
UH, CAN SHE GET
YOUR NUMBER?
SURE.
CALL ME ANY TIME
YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS.
JUST DON'T CALL ME
ON YOUR CELLPHONE.
[LAUGHS]
NOW, SEE, WHY DID I HAVE
TO GO BACK TO THAT?
I'M LEAVING
BEFORE YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND.
OH, HAPPILY MARRIED,
HAPPILY MARRIED,
HAPPILY MARRIED.
Jane: WE'RE LATE.
WE HAVE WINE AND FLOWERS
TO MAKE UP FOR IT.
YEAH, BUT WE
WOULDN'T BE LATE
IF WE HADN'T STOPPED
FOR THE WINE AND FLOWERS.
AH, THE CLASSIC
DINNER PARTY DILEMMA.
OK. HERE WE GO.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
HEY, EL.
[SMOOCHES]
THANK YOU,
WOW--HI.
HI.
I'M NOAH.
JANE.
COME ON IN.
Jane: THANKS FOR
DOING THIS.
I ALWAYS FEEL BADLY
WHEN MY DATING LIFE
STARTS TO AFFECT THE LIVES
OF INNOCENT BYSTANDERS.
YEAH, WELL, UH,
UNFORTUNATELY,
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL YOU.
UH, [CLEARS THROAT]
GRANT GOT HERE EARLY
AND I MAY HAVE MENTIONED
THAT THIS IS A SET-UP.
NOAH...
HE WAS DRESSED ALL WRONG,
I HAD NO CHOICE.
ANYWAY, HE'S BEEN GETTING
MORE AND MORE NERVOUS,
SO HE'S NOT
IN THE BEST SHAPE.
OK.
JANE, UH, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HAVE SOME APPETIZERS
WITH GRANT
IN THE LIVING ROOM?
AND, EL, UH, WILLOW AND I COULD
USE SOME HELP IN THE KITCHEN.
THANK YOU.
HI, UH,
I'M JANE GRANT.
I'M--I'M GRANT.
HI, NICE
TO MEET YOU, GRANT.
YOU CAN'T
BE GRANT.
I'M JANE.
SO WHY'D YOU SAY
YOUR NAME WAS GRANT?
GRANT'S MY LAST NAME.
[Laughing]
OH, THAT'S PRETTY FUNNY.
I GUESS.
WE'RE BOTH GRANTS.
RIGHT.
IF WE GOT MARRIED, YOU KNOW,
YOUR NAME WOULD BE GRANT GRANT.
NO, IT WOULD
STILL BE JANE.
MMM, MMM--
OH, OH, I GET IT, I GET IT.
YOU'RE ONE OF THOSE WOMEN.
MY FIRST NAME'S JANE,
SO THAT WOULDN'T CHANGE
REGARDLESS OF WHAT HAPPENED
TO MY LAST NAME,
WHICH IS GRANT.
YOU'RE PRETTY FUNNY
FOR A FEMINIST.
WE'RE HAVING KEBABS
FOR DINNER--
FOOD THAT'S AS MUCH FUN TO SAY
AS IT IS TO EAT.
WHOA.
EXCUSE ME?
I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL.
THANK YOU.
I KNOW I PROBABLY
SHOULDN'T JUST COME OUT
AND SAY IT LIKE THAT,
BUT IT'S TOO POWERFUL--
YOU ARE STUNNING.
WELL, YOU'RE
A REALLY LUCKY MAN--
YOU'RE IN A ROOMFUL
OF HOT WOMEN THEN.
CAREFUL--
FEMINISTS LIKE GRANT
DON'T LIKE IT WHEN
YOU NOTICE THEIR LOOKS.
CAN I GET YOU
A DRINK?
PLEASE--
I'M SURE JANE
COULD USE ONE, TOO.
WHO?
NEVER MIND.
HEY NATASHA, IT'S JANE--
BUT YOU PROBABLY
RECOGNIZE MY VOICE
FROM THE OTHER 20 MESSAGES.
SO I HAVEN'T HEARD
FROM YOU ALL WEEK.
IT'S PROBABLY BECAUSE
YOU'RE SLAVING AWAY
ON THE CHAPTER--
THE CHAPTER
YOU'RE GIVING ME TODAY?
SO CALL ME AND WE'LL MAKE
ARRANGEMENTS ON GETTING IT HERE.
I'M HAPPY TO SEND A MESSENGER
OR THE SPACE SHUTTLE
OR WHATEVER--
JUST LET ME KNOW.
THANK YOU, BYE.
HEY!
HEY, MAX.
WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
I'M REALLY NOT SURE.
AMANDA THINKS SHE NEEDS
TO COOK FOR JEFF.
WHAT'S JEFF THINK?
WELL, THERE'S A LOT
OF LEFTOVERS.
[LAUGHS]
LISTEN, REMKE WANTED ME
TO CHECK IN--
MAKE SURE NATASHA GAVE YOU
THE FIRST CHAPTER.
I ASSURED HIM
YOU HAD IT UNDER CONTROL.
OF COURSE!
[LAUGHS]
GOOD.
BECAUSE MARIE CLAIRE
IS NOT BUDGING AT ALL
ON THAT DEADLINE,
SO I'M GONNA NEED
THE EXCERPT OF THE FIRST
CHAPTER ON MONDAY.
THAT'S WHAT
I WAS PLANNING.
LIFE WAS SO MUCH EASIER
BEFORE I BECAME A GERMAPHOBE.
HEY, MAX,
YOU JOINING US?
UH, NO, SORRY,
I GOTTA RUN.
SMELLS GREAT,
THOUGH.
Remke: MORGAN,
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I NEED THOSE NEW COVERS.
OH, WHAT HAPPENED?!
YOU SET IT FOR, LIKE,
9,000 MINUTES!
I LIED TO MAX.
I NEVER LIE TO MAX.
I KNOW--THAT WAS
ALWAYS YOUR PROBLEM.
WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
OH, WHEN YOU'RE
IN A RELATIONSHIP
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH
BENDING THE TRUTH A LITTLE
TO SHOW YOURSELF
IN A FAVORABLE LIGHT.
YOU DO REALIZE THAT THE WOMAN
WHO WROTE THE RULES
GOT A DIVORCE?
POOR ELLEN!
AT LEAST SHE'LL GET TO SLEEP
WITH NEW GUYS!
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
OH, THAT BETTER BE THE GNAT--
OR THE FIREMAN
WHO RESCUED HER
FROM THE BOOKCASE
SHE'S BEEN TRAPPED UNDER.
JANE GRANT.
HEY, JANE--
IT'S DANA.
OH, HI, DANA.
GET OUT YOUR
PALM PILOT.
I DON'T HAVE
A PALM PILOT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU DON'T HAVE A PALM PILOT?
EVERYONE HAS
A PALM PILOT.
I USE POST-ITS.
OK, WELL, I NEED TO
GO OVER THE SCHEDULE OF
BRIDESMAIDS' ACTIVITIES.
NOW, I'M SURE YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE FINAL
DRESS FITTING, SLASH
PRE-SHOWER MEETING
THIS WEEKEND.
PRE-SHOWER?
TO DISCUSS THE SHOWER.
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
RIGHT.
AND THEN THERE'S THE SHOWER
ITSELF ON THE 16th--
THE THEME IS GONNA BE
"FRENCH KITCHEN" IN HONOR
OF OUR HONEYMOON IN FRANCE.
JANE GRANT.
HELLO, TIMOTHY ROMMELLY!
32, UPPER EAST SIDE, DOCTOR!
AND, OF COURSE,
THE BACHELORETTE PARTY
ON THE 28th.
UH, LISTEN, DANA,
I'M GONNA TRY TO MAKE IT
TO AS MANY THINGS AS POSSIBLE,
BUT IT'S A VERY BUSY--
IF I PLAN EVENTS
EVERY DAY OF THE WEEK,
I EXPECT YOU
TO BE THERE.
IT COMES WITH THE HONOR
OF BEING A BRIDESMAID.
I KNOW IT MUST BE HARD FOR YOU
TO SEE ME GETTING MARRIED
WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE
ANYBODY SERIOUS--
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND!
RIGHT--I FORGOT.
IT MUST BE BECAUSE
I'VE NEVER MET HIM
OR SEEN A PICTURE OF HIM
OR EVEN HEARD HIS NAME.
BY THE WAY,
WHAT IS HIS NAME, JANE?
TIMOTHY ROMMELLY.
GREAT, WELL, I'LL HAVE
THE CALLIGRAPHER PUT
THAT ON HIS NAME CARD.
UH, 2 M'S, 2 L'S?
SURE!
GREAT, SEE YOU
AT THE PRE-SHOWER!
CAN'T WAIT.
DINNER, MONDAY,
PARK TERRACE CAFE.
I'M NOT HAPPY ABOUT
THE LACK OF LEAD TIME,
BUT I MADE AN EXCEPTION
DUE TO THE DIRE CIRCUMSTANCES.
OH, GOOD, BECAUSE MY LIFE
WASN'T FULL ENOUGH
HAVING A WRITER
WHO'S GONE MISSING
AND AN ARRAY OF BRIDESMAIDS'
ACTIVITIES SO VAST
THAT EVEN LIZ TAYLOR
WOULD SAY,
"OH, HEY,
IT'S ONLY A WEDDING."
YOU ARE NOT THINKING
OF BACKING OUT OF
THE DATES, ARE YOU?
I HAVE 3 WEEKS
TO FIND A GUY, DATE HIM,
BECOME BOYFRIEND
AND GIRLFRIEND,
TALK HIM INTO GOING
TO THE PRINCESS' WEDDING,
AND THEN, DEPENDING ON THE GUY,
DEVELOP A LEVEL OF COMFORT
WHERE I COULD ASK HIM,
"HEY, DO YOU MIND POSING AS
AN UPPER EAST SIDE DOCTOR?"
I AM SO PROUD OF YOU.
[SIGHS]
THANKS.
GIRLS,
DANA AND I FOUND
THESE LOVELY
CHAMPAGNE-COLORED EARRINGS
AND YOU'RE GONNA SEE--
THEY'RE GONNA GO SO PERFECTLY
NOW I TRIED
TO TELL MOM
THAT THE CHAMPAGNE
PARASOLS WERE ENOUGH,
BUT SHE WOULDN'T
LISTEN.
WELL, YOUR DAUGHTER
ONLY GETS MARRIED ONCE--
GOD WILLING--
AND I DON'T SEE THE HARM
IN HAVING JUST A LITTLE BIT
OF COLOR COORDINATION,
DO YOU?
WELL, ALL WE NEED
NOW IS THE DYED
POODLE TO MATCH.
OH, MY GOD--
I WANTED THAT
AT MY WEDDING,
BUT THOSE CRAZY
ANIMAL PEOPLE
WOULDN'T LET ME.
SO, GIRLS, I MEAN,
THERE'S SO MANY OF YOU,
SO I THINK THE BEST THING
TO DO IS TO LINE UP
ACCORDING
TO YOUR SIZE.
MOTHER!
HONEY, WE CAN'T KEEP
THE DRESSES IN ORDER IF WE--
FINE, WE'LL JUST DO IT
ALPHABETICALLY.
[LAUGHTER]
SO, WHAT'S SHE LIKE?
WHO?
NATASHA!
OH, WELL,
I, UM--
GEORGE CLOONEY, HMM?
EXCUSE ME?
IS THAT WHO
THE ACTOR IS?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
OH, I WON'T
SAY ANYTHING.
NO, I REALLY
DON'T KNOW.
[Sighing]
OK.
[GASPS]
PIERCE BROSNAN!
SO, SHE'S NICE?
SHE SEEMS REALLY NICE.
AND SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
IS SHE AS BEAUTIFUL
IN PERSON?
Dana: YOU CAN SEE
FOR YOURSELF--
NATASHA IS COMING
TO THE WEDDING.
REALLY?
OF COURSE! WHY WOULDN'T
I HAVE A MOVIE STAR
AT MY DAUGHTER'S
WEDDING?
THAT'LL BE SO EXCITING
TO HAVE A TRUE CELEBRITY THERE.
OH, WE SHOULD INVITE HER
TO THE SHOWER!
DO YOU THINK
SHE'D COME?
OH, JANE, YOU INVITE HER--
YOU GUYS ARE FRIENDS.
NO, ACTUALLY,
WE'RE NOT FRIENDS.
WE JUST WORK TOGETHER--
AND THAT'S
WHEN SHE BOTHERS
TO CALL ME BACK.
GREEN-EYED MONSTER,
PARTY OF ONE!
Dana: I'LL
CALL HER!
I'M SURE SHE'D
LOVE TO COME!
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
WHAT?
NOTHING.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
YOU CAN TELL ME,
REALLY.
DID YOU KNOW THAT
ONE OF YOUR HIPS
IS HIGHER THAN THE OTHER?
NO--NO,
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
WELL, IT'S NO PICNIC
TO DEAL WITH.
[INDISTINCT TALKING]
COULD YOU HELP ME
PICK UP THAT WRAPPER?
I CAN'T BEND
THE WAY I USED TO.
OH, SURE.
[LAUGHS]
THANK YOU.
I'M HERBERT.
OH, JANE.
ARE YOU LOOKING
FOR A PARTNER?
OH, NO, I-I'M LOOKING
FOR MY FRIEND GARY.
OH, THAT'S TOO BAD--
YOU'RE A GOOD BENDER.
Gary: JANE!
HI!
HELLO,
I'M SO GLAD YOU
COULD MAKE IT.
YEAH, ME TOO.
THANKS FOR THE INVITATION.
OF COURSE!
THIS IS GONNA BE GREAT,
JUST GREAT--
GOOD PEOPLE,
GOOD CHARITY.
LOOK AT THE TURNOUT!
THIS IS OUR GROUP?
YEAH.
[LAUGHS]
YEAH, I GUESS WE TARGETED
THE AARP A LITTLE STRONG.
NEXT TIME WE'LL HAVE TO
CAST A WIDER NET.
WELL, I GUESS
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
STICK TOGETHER.
I GUESS SO.
SO ARE YOU READY
TO GET STARTED?
YEAH, SURE.
YOU KNOW, I BROUGHT
SOME SUNSCREEN IN
CASE YOU NEED IT.
LOOK AT YOU--A PRO ALREADY.
SUNSCREEN'S A GREAT IDEA.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN NEVER BE TOO CAREFUL.
JUST 'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT
LYING AT A BEACH
DOESN'T MEAN YOU DON'T
NEED PROTECTION--
ESPECIALLY ON THOSE
LITTLE AREAS LIKE THE EARS
AND THE HANDS
AND THE, UM--TORSO.
WE REALLY NEED
THAT SUNSCREEN NOW.
OK--OH!
CAN I HELP YOU?
I GOT IT.
IT'S OK.
OK, ALL RIGHT.
[LAUGHS]
YOU JUST STAND THERE
AND LOOK FABULOUS.
I MEANT TO THROW AWAY
THIS HALF-EATEN SANDWICH.
THE WHOLE WORLD'S
ON DISPLAY HERE.
YEAH, OK.
HERE WE GO--
SUNSCREEN...
JANE, THIS IS
MY GIRLFRIEND, CASSANDRA.
HI.
HI! IT'S SO GREAT
THAT YOU COULD MAKE IT.
COULD I GET YOUR HELP
AT THE WATER TABLE?
FOR SOME REASON
WE'VE GOT A REALLY
THIRSTY GROUP TODAY.
FOR SOME REASON?
LOOK AT THE HOTTIE
HANDING OUT WATER.
FOR SOME REASON?
CATCH UP
WITH YOU LATER.
SO, HERBERT,
STILL NEED THAT PARTNER?
OH, I'VE ALREADY
FOUND SOMEONE.
OH, WHEN YOU SNOOZE,
YOU LOSE, SWEETHEART.
♪ I'VE BEEN RIGHT ♪
♪ AND I'VE BEEN WRONG... ♪
SO?
REALLY.
HEY, COJO SAYS THAT
ANIMAL PRINTS ARE IN.
AND IF I WERE TRYING
TO ATTRACT A GAY MAN
OR A LEOPARD,
I'D BE RIGHT THERE
WITH HIM.
HEY, NATASHA,
IT'S JANE.
JUST CHECKING IN--
AGAIN.
LISTEN, WE'RE ON
A REALLY TIGHT DEADLINE.
I NEED YOUR FIRST CHAPTER
YESTERDAY--LITERALLY.
UM, IF I DON'T GET THE PIECE,
MARIE CLAIRE IS GONNA PULL IT.
SO, WHY DON'T YOU
GIVE ME A CALL.
I'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
THANKS!
SHE'S SCREENING ME.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
BLASTING GUNS N' ROSES
INTO HER MACHINE
UNTIL SHE CAN'T BEAR IT
ANYMORE AND IS FORCED
TO COME OUT OF HIDING?
HMM, THE NORIEGA
APPROACH.
OR YOU COULD FORGET
HER AND JUST WRITE
THE MEMOIRS YOURSELF.
AH, FIRST CHAPTER--
"WHO AM I SLEEPING WITH TODAY?"
"WELL, IT'S TUESDAY--
IT MUST BE A CASTING DIRECTOR."
"AND THEN IF I GET THE PART,
IT'S MY LEADING MAN,
MY DIRECTOR, AND THE KID
WHO BRINGS ME COFFEE."
"OH, ONLY IF IT'S
THE STUDIO HEAD'S KID."
SO, SERIOUSLY, WHAT HAPPENS
IF SHE DOESN'T TURN UP?
I'VE SCOPED OUT A FEW PLACES
IN THE PARK THAT LOOK COZY.
SHE REALLY...
YEAH, THAT'S
CHAPTER 2.
ALL RIGHT, HERE IT IS--
THE OUTFIT THAT SAYS,
"HANK CHILTON,
MY PENULTIMATE SHOT,
"YOU ARE GONNA FIND ME
SO CHARMING,
"WITTY, AND SEXY
BUT CLASSY
"THAT YOU WILL HAVE
NO CHOICE BUT TO FALL
MADLY IN LOVE WITH ME
OR AT LEAST GO
TO THE WEDDING
AND PRETEND."
THAT IS ONE
CHATTY OUTFIT.
CAN IT GO ON THE DATE
WITHOUT ME?
[SIGHS]
WHERE IS YOUR ENTHUSIASM?
I DON'T KNOW.
WE'VE COME THIS FAR.
YOU REALLY WANNA LET
DANA AND THE GNAT THINK
THEY'RE BETTER
THAN YOU JUST 'CAUSE
THEY HAVE BOYFRIENDS?
NO. BUT DON'T
YOU THINK IT'S JUST
A LITTLE PATHETIC
TO BE DOING ALL THIS
AT MY AGE?
NO--IT'S
USUALLY PATHETIC.
BUT IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT--
IT'S THEM.
THEY'RE THE ONES WHO
ONLY HAVE ONE MEASURE
FOR GAUGING WHETHER OR NOT
A WOMAN IS A SUCCESS.
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
SO YOU'RE GONNA BEAT THEM
AT THEIR OWN GAME.
YEAH?
YOU ARE GONNA SHOW UP
AT THAT WEDDING
WITH A BOYFRIEND SO FABULOUS
THAT DANA WILL EXPERIENCE
HER VERY FIRST
TWINGE OF REGRET
AT BEING MARRIED.
HA HA!
AND YOU ARE GONNA FIND
THAT BOYFRIEND
TONIGHT AT NATE'S.
ALL RIGHT!
AND YOU'RE GONNA DO IT
WEARING THE LEOPARD TOP.
NO!
SO I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY THAT'S THE ONLY TABLE
YOU CAN GIVE ME!
I-I MEAN, IT'S 2 FEET
FROM THE BATHROOM!
SIR--
I MEAN, I THINK
THE HEALTH DEPARTMENT
WOULD HAVE A THING OR 2
TO SAY ABOUT THIS, DON'T YOU?
WELL, I'M SORRY,
BUT WE ARE FULL.
OH, SO I GET
THE...TABLE.
OH, HOW 'BOUT THAT COUPLE
OVER THERE--WHY DON'T YOU
GIVE IT TO THEM?
THEY'RE FROM JERSEY--
THEY'LL FEEL RIGHT AT HOME!
AND HOW 'BOUT THAT GUY
OVER THERE?
HE WON'T KNOW THE DIFFERENCE--
HE'S PRACTICALLY BLIND!
HEY, STEVIE WONDER!
GOT A TABLE OVER THERE FOR YA!
KEEP YOUR VOICE
DOWN, PLEASE.
HI, NATASHA, IT'S JANE AGAIN.
IF YOU'RE THERE,
WILL YOU PICK UP?
NO, OK.
WELL, UM, CALL ME.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
I KNOW I MENTIONED THAT BEFORE
TO NO AVAIL,
BUT, UH, I'M KIND
OF AT A LOSS HERE.
UM, YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE JUST
ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
THAT DON'T LIKE PHONES,
I'M OPEN TO OTHER MODES
OF COMMUNICATION--
E-MAIL, INSTANT MESSAGE.
I'LL EVEN HIRE A GUY
TO TAP IT OUT IN MORSE CODE.
BYE.
NATASHA?
HI.
I'M SORRY TO BARGE
IN ON YOU.
NO, THAT'S OK.
COME IN.
I WASN'T SURE I'D FIND YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU'D PROBABLY BE
AT YOUR...BOYFRIEND'S.
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
I USUALLY AM.
AS YOU CAN SEE, IT LOOKS LIKE
A 22-YEAR-OLD LIVES HERE
'CAUSE THAT'S THE LAST TIME
I WAS HERE.
CAN I GET YOU ANYTHING?
ICED TEA WOULD BE GREAT.
OK.
WELL, IT WOULD BE.
I THINK
THE ONLY OPTIONS ARE
LOW-SODIUM SOY SAUCE
OR WATER.
WATER IS FINE.
SO I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM YOU
IN A WHILE.
I'M ASSUMING THERE'S
BEEN SOME KIND OF
WRITER'S BLOCK GOING ON.
FOR FUTURE REFERENCE,
I CAN HELP YOU WITH THAT,
BUT I CAN'T HELP YOU
IF YOU HIDE FROM ME.
I'M PREGNANT.
WHAT DOES
YOUR BOYFRIEND SAY?
SAM'S...AMAZING.
YOU KNOW, FIRST HE WAS
A SAINT AFTER THE MESS
WITH THE ACTOR,
AND NOW THIS COMES ALONG,
AND HE COULDN'T BE
MORE THRILLED.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
YEAH, IT IS.
I SHOULD BE GRATEFUL.
IT'S JUST THIS IS NOT
WHAT I HAD PLANNED.
YOU KNOW, NOT NOW.
NOT WHEN MY OWN LIFE
IS SO SCREWED UP.
YOUR LIFE IS NOT SCREWED UP.
I AM A WASHED-UP ACTOR
WHO'S ONLY KNOWN AT ALL
BECAUSE OF AN AFFAIR
I HAD OVER A YEAR AGO
WITH A REAL ACTOR.
YEAH, I'M DOING GREAT.
I DON'T KNOW THE FIRST THING
ABOUT BEING A MOM.
WHAT IF I SCREW THAT UP TOO?
YOU WON'T.
I DON'T.
[LAUGHS]
BUT IF YOU DO SCREW
YOUR KID UP,
THERE IS A WHOLE INDUSTRY
OF THERAPISTS OUT THERE
THAT ARE JUST WAITING
TO HELP.
EVERYONE SCREWS UP,
WHICH IS ACTUALLY
NORMAL, RIGHT?
NOT SCREWING UP WOULD BE
THE WEIRD THING,
SO LET'S HOPE YOU
SCREW UP, MISSY.
I'M SORRY FOR
THE DISAPPEARING ACT.
I JUST COULDN'T TALK
TO ANYONE, BUT I DO HAVE
THE FIRST CHAPTER.
WOW, THAT'S AMAZING
CONSIDERING EVERYTHING
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH.
IS THIS IS IT?
SHE'S GONNA GET FAT.
STOP IT.
DO THEY MAKE LEATHER
MATERNITY PANTS?
I ACTUALLY FEEL
KIND OF BAD FOR HER.
OH, COME ON!
SHE TOTALLY YOU OVER.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO HAVE
A WEEK TO DO YOUR EXCERPT.
YOU HAD ONE NIGHT.
SO I'LL BILL HER FOR
THE RED BULL I MAINLINED.
MORGAN, I NEED TO ORDER SOME
OFFICE SUPPLIES, PLEASE.
YEAH, YOU'VE EXCEEDED
YOUR MONTHLY LIMIT.
WE'VE CUT YOU OFF.
WHAT?
AND, UH, WILLIAM
WOULD LIKE TO SEE
YOU RIGHT AWAY.
OH, OK.
DON'T WORRY.
NO ONE'S EVER BEEN FIRED
FOR USING TOO MANY POST-ITS,
AT LEAST NOT YET.
UH, HELLO.
WE HAVEN'T GOT ALL DAY.
SIT DOWN.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE EVERYTHING'S
OK WITH THE NUTLEY PROJECT.
YES, AS FAR
AS I'M CONCERNED.
IT'S NOT ALWAYS SMOOTH EVERY
STEP OF THE WAY,
BUT AS LONG AS EVERYTHING
TURNS OUT OK,
WHO NEEDS TO KNOW ABOUT
THE PROBLEMS?
WHICH PROBABLY
MAKES YOU WONDER WHY
I BROUGHT THEM UP.
JANE'S DOING GREAT.
I READ THE FIRST CHAPTER
THIS MORNING
AND THE OUTLINE
FOR 2 AND 3,
AND IT'S RIGHT ON TRACK
WITH WHAT WE WANT,
AND THE EXCERPT FROM
MARIE CLAIRE --PERFECT.
IS THAT TRUE, GRANT?
YES, I'M ACTUALLY
QUITE PLEASED
WITH HOW EVERYTHING IS
TURNING OUT.
WELL, SO AM I.
REALLY?
THAT'S WHY I SAID IT.
OF COURSE.
I WANT YOU TO WRITE
THE BACK COVER COPY.
DO A GOOD JOB.
DO IT FAST.
I WILL. THANK YOU.
MAX, YOU STAY.
THERE'S SOMETHING I NEED
TO DISCUSS WITH YOU.
SO...YOU KNOW I HAVEN'T THOUGHT
ABOUT ME AND MAX
FOR A WHILE NOW.
UH-OH.
I JUST GOT CALLED IN
TO SEE REMKE
AND AS USUAL I GOT
COMPLETELY TONGUE-TIED,
BUT MAX STEPPED IN
AND SAVED ME.
HE RAVED ABOUT MY WORK, AND
REMKE ENDED UP RAVING AS WELL.
JANE, THAT'S GREAT!
I KNOW.
THAT'S ABOUT YOU, NOT MAX.
[SIGHS] WELL, IT'S JUST THAT
HE KNOWS ME SO WELL,
AND HE MAKES ME FEEL...SAFE.
IT DIDN'T WORK
BETWEEN YOU GUYS.
BUT IS IT WORKING
THAT MUCH BETTER NOW?
I MEAN ANY PROBLEMS WE HAD
IN THE PAST SEEM PRETTY MINOR
COMPARED TO GUYS
WITH GIRLFRIENDS,
AND GUYS WHO RUN OVER
THEIR EXs,
AND GUYS
WHO ARE DRIVEN TO DRINK
BY THE MERE THOUGHT
OF DATING ME, AND--
YOU'RE IN THE TOAD PHASE.
IT'S JUST PART
OF MOVING FORWARD.
I DON'T KNOW.
MOVING BACKWARDS TO SEE
IF THINGS COULD WORK OUT
BETWEEN MAX AND I IS SOUNDING
BETTER AND BETTER.
WELL, I DON'T WANT
TO KEEP DATING!
MY ONLY OTHER OPTION IS TO BUY
A DOZEN CATS AND CALL IT A DAY.
JANE, YOU'RE WANTED
IN THE CONFERENCE ROOM.
YOU CAN COME TOO.
THANKS.
[LAUGHTER]
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
I MEAN IT'S PROBABLY
INSANE, BUT...
OH, MY GOD!
YOU'RE BEING PROMOTED!
MAYBE.
THAT HAS TO BE IT.
YOU JUST SAID REMKE RAVED.
REMKE NEVER RAVES.
I KNOW, AND HE ASKED MAX TO STAY
AFTER TO DISCUSS SOMETHING.
IT'S ABOUT TIME!
WE'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS FOREVER!
OK, YOU LOOK GREAT!
LET'S GO,
MISS ASSOCIATE EDITOR.
OH, MY GOD.
[CLEARS THROAT]
THANK YOU ALL FOR GATHERING
LIKE THIS.
UM, I HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT THAT
ON A PERSONAL LEVEL
I FEEL VERY LUCKY
TO BE ABLE TO DELIVER.
I'M HAPPY TO ANNOUNCE THAT I'M
ENGAGED TO BE MARRIED
TO CAROLYN KLAUSNER.
SOME OF YOU KNOW HER,
BUT FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO DON'T,
SHE'S AN EXECUTIVE
VICE-PRESIDENT AT
METROPOLITAN SCENE,
BUT MORE IMPORTANTLY SHE'S
THE WOMAN OF MY DREAMS.
SHE'S NOT HERE, MAX.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY
THE SAPPY STUFF.
TO MAX'S ENGAGEMENT.
I GUESS
I'LL KEEP DATING.
MM-HMM.
JANE GRANT?
HI, UH, TIMOTHY?
YEAH.
OH, HI.
HI.
YOU'RE EARLY.
SO ARE YOU.
UH, I GUESS THAT'S ONE THING
WE HAVE IN COMMON, HUH?
I THOUGHT I WOULD SQUEEZE IN
A LITTLE WORK.
I DIDN'T MEAN FOR YOU
TO CATCH ME. SORRY.
OH, THAT'S OK.
I UNDERSTAND.
IN FACT I SHOULDN'T ADMIT
TO THIS,
BUT I BROUGHT SOME
OF MY WORK TOO
IN CASE YOU ENDED UP
BEING LATE.
WOW!
AND ALREADY WE'RE THE WORLD'S
MOST BORING COUPLE.
YEAH, WE MOVED RIGHT PAST
BUTTERFLIES
INTO COMFORTABLY IGNORING
EACH OTHER.
I'M SORRY.
DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
[CHUCKLES]
SO, UM, HOW LONG HAVE YOU HAD
THIS FEAR OF DOWNTIME?
MMM. I TRACE IT BACK
TO A PIVOTAL SUBWAY BREAKDOWN
IN WHICH I HAD NO
READING MATERIALS.
OH, THAT SOUNDS TRAUMATIC.
MM-HMM. IT ALTERED
THE COURSE OF MY LIFE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
YEAH, 36 HOURS IN AN AIRPORT
DURING A BLIZZARD.
OUCH.
MY STORY'S NOTHING COMPARED
TO YOURS.
WELL, THIS MAY SOUND
A LITTLE WEIRD,
BUT IF YOU WANT TO KEEP TONIGHT
SHORT TO FINISH YOUR WORK,
I'D TOTALLY UNDERSTAND.
NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FORWARD
TO MEETING YOU.
YOU HAVE?
YEAH. WHY IS THAT
SO HARD TO BELIEVE?
I'M JUST A LITTLE SURPRISED
TO HEAR YOU SAY IT.
NOBODY'S REALLY THAT DIRECT.
WELL, THEN IN THE INTEREST
OF DIRECTNESS,
I SHOULD PROBABLY TELL YOU
THAT I LIED TO YOU EARLIER.
OH.
I HAVEN'T MOVED PAST
BUTTERFLIES YET.
OH.
♪ NA-NA-NA NA-NA-NA-NA NA-NA ♪
♪ BEYOND COMPARE,
CAN'T HELP BUT STARE ♪
♪ SO FULL OF LIFE ♪
♪ INSPIRED,
LIKE A LONELY CHILD ♪
♪ YOU'RE MAGICAL ♪
♪ YOUR BLESSED STARE,
I APPRECIATE ♪
♪ YOU STOP THE CLOUDS
FROM CRYING... ♪
I'M GLAD YOU TALKED
ME INTO STAYING
OUT TONIGHT.
WELL, YOU KNOW, THE FACT THAT
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN TAXI DRIVER
NEEDED TO BE CORRECTED
IMMEDIATELY, OK.
YEAH, IT WAS GREAT.
I LOVE AL PACINO.
WHAT?
THAT WAS ROBERT DeNIRO.
RIGHT! I ALWAYS GET
THOSE 2 MIXED UP!
PLEASE TELL ME
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
UH-OH. I SHOULD BE SMART
AND STOP HERE, SHOULDN'T I?
THEY'RE 2 OF THE GREATEST
ACTORS OF OUR TIME.
HOW COULD YOU
GET THEM MIXED UP?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT PROUD OF IT.
OK. WHICH ONE WAS IT
THAT WAS IN TOOTSIE?
THAT WAS DUSTIN HOFFMAN.
[LAUGHS]
THIS IS A DEAL-BREAKER,
ISN'T IT?
YOU'RE A NUT.
COULD I SELL YOU ON
LOVABLE NEUROTIC?
WELL, LET ME
THINK ABOUT THAT.
♪ YOU CRAZY THING,
YOU'RE SO SEXUAL ♪
♪ YOU STOP THE FLOWERS
FROM DYING, I'M SIGHING ♪
♪ BUT YOU DON'T SEE
WHO YOU ARE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU MEAN ♪
♪ I WISH YOU... ♪
LOVABLE NEUROTIC WORKS FINE.
♪ ...'CAUSE I DON'T... ♪
♪ BEAUTIFUL YOU ♪
♪ OH, BABY,
WON'T YOU COME MY WAY? ♪
♪ YOUR BEAUTY'S TRUE ♪
♪ DON'T LISTEN
TO WHAT FOOLS MIGHT SAY ♪
♪ BEAUTIFUL YOU ♪
ARE YOU WORKING?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT SOMETIMES YOU
COULD BE LOOKING AT THE PAGE
AND REALLY YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT
PUPPIES OR TOAST
OR HOW WEIRD IT IS
THAT YOU HATE RAP,
BUT YOU THINK EMINEM
IS SO SEXY.
YEAH, THAT'S JUST ME.
BUT COME ON, WE NEED MORE
ON THE TIMOTHY DATE.
I TOLD YOU IT WAS GOOD.
GOOD-GOOD OR JUST GOOD ENOUGH
CONSIDERING THE TICKING CLOCK?
GOOD-GOOD.
WOW!
YOU KNOW, HE'S A REALLY GREAT
GUY AND A DOCTOR,
SO HE TOTALLY FITS THE LIE.
IS HE A GOOD KISSER?
YOU KNOW WHAT
WOULD BE IRONIC
IS IF I ACTUALLY
WENT THROUGH WITH THIS
AND GOT A DATE
FOR THE WEDDING,
BUT THEN COULDN'T
SHOW MY FACE
BECAUSE I HAD BEEN
FIRED FOR NOT GETTING
MY WORK DONE.
SHUTTING UP NOW.
HE'S A REALLY GOOD KISSER.
[CHUCKLES]
HA HA HA!
ALL RIGHT, I'LL ANSWER
TO CATHERINE DeNEUVE,
BRIGITTE BARDOT,
BUT I DRAW THE LINE
AT EDITH PIAF.
ACTUALLY I'M LAUGHING AT
THE FACT YOU'RE HERE AGAIN.
YOU LOG MORE HOURS THAN I DO.
OH, WELL, I'M GLAD YOU FIND
MY PAIN AMUSING.
OH, I DO,
AND IF I KNEW YOU BETTER, I
WOULD TOTALLY MOCK THE BERET.
3 WORDS--
THEMED BRIDAL SHOWER.
OHH!
CAN I HELP YOU OUT
WITH A SUDDEN DEBILITATING
BLOW TO THE HEAD?
THAT'S SO SWEET.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST CHECK
THE REGISTRY.
OH, WAIT, NO!
I'M OVER REGISTRIES.
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST
NOT FAIR THAT
JUST 'CAUSE YOU'RE
GETTING MARRIED
YOU GET TO HAND PEOPLE LISTS
AND SAY BUY ME THIS STUFF
AND NO ONE FINDS THIS
PRESUMPTUOUS.
WHAT? YOU DON'T AGREE?
YOU'RE NOT GOING SOFT ON ME,
ARE YOU?
IT JUST REALLY HARD
TO TAKE YOU SERIOUSLY
WHEN YOU LOOK LIKE
A GONDOLIER.
HOW IS THIS MY LIFE?
HEY, MAYBE YOU SHOULD TAKE
THE "IF YOU CAN'T BEAT 'EM,
JOIN 'EM" APPROACH.
AND WHAT--SHACK UP
WITH SOME RANDOM GUY
IN ORDER TO GET PRESENTS?
NO, JUST REGISTER YOURSELF
FOR LIKE YOUR 30th BIRTHDAY.
[SIGHS] OH, RIGHT,
BECAUSE I JUST DON'T HAVE ENOUGH
HUMILIATION IN MY LIFE.
WELL, THEN BUY YOURSELF
SOMETHING NICE,
YOU KNOW, TO GET THROUGH
ALL THIS.
AN ISLAND.
WELL, I WAS THINKING
CHAMPAGNE GLASSES.
THEY MAKE
A NICE STATEMENT
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE LOTS OF THINGS
TO CELEBRATE,
YOU'RE A REALLY GOOD
SALESPERSON.
SHH. KEEP IT DOWN.
I'M STILL HOPING TO ESCAPE
THIS PLACE ONE DAY.
I FOR ONE AM SO RELIEVED--
OVER A YEAR OF PLANNING!
THANK GOD THIS WEDDING
IS IN 2 WEEKS!
OVER A YEAR OF PLANNING!
IT'S BEEN MORE LIKE 24 YEARS.
YOU USED TO READ ME EXCERPTS
FROM MODERN BRIDE.
SO, NATASHA, WE'RE SO GLAD
YOU COULD FIT US
INTO YOUR GLAMOROUS LIFE.
OH, I DON'T KNOW
HOW GLAMOROUS IT IS.
IF I WASN'T HERE, I'D BE SITTING
AT HOME WRITING IN MY PJs.
A FAMOUS ACTRESS
AND SHE'S MODEST.
WELL, I'M JUST SO EXCITED
TO BE A PART OF THIS
'CAUSE IT'S NOT EVERY DAY
THAT DANA GETS MARRIED,
AT LEAST WE HOPE.
HA HA HA!
YES, WE DO!
SO, SPEAKING OF WEDDINGS,
I HEARD ABOUT MAX.
MAX FROM...WORK?
HE'S JANE'S EX.
OH, I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
YEAH, MAX JUST GOT ENGAGED
TO A GORGEOUS VP
AT COSMOPOLITAN SCENE.
NO, IT'S OK, REALLY.
[LAUGHS] I WISH HIM THE BEST.
WELL, IT'S GOOD THAT YOU
AT LEAST HAVE TIMOTHY.
AND I FEEL VERY LUCKY
TO HAVE HIM IN MY LIFE.
WELL, GOOD. I LOOK FORWARD
TO MEETING HIM AT THE WEDDING.
THANK YOU.
AND OF COURSE, YOU KNOW,
IF THINGS DON'T WORK OUT,
ETHAN MILES
IS STILL AVAILABLE.
[LAUGHTER]
RIGHT.
EXCUSE ME.
I'M GONNA GET MORE CREPES.
REMEMBER, YOU STILL HAVE TO FIT
INTO YOUR BRIDESMAID DRESS.
I'M SO SORRY ABOUT MAX.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU GUYS USED
TO BE AN ITEM.
WHY DIDN'T TELL ME?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST NOT
A VERY BIG DEAL.
WELL, I'M AROUND IF YOU EVER
WANT TO TALK.
WOW. THANKS, BUT I'M GOOD.
SO HOW IS EVERYTHING GOING?
OK, YOU KNOW, JUST SLOWLY
GETTING USED TO THE IDEA
OF BEING PREGNANT AND STUFF.
I GUESS I'M GONNA HAVE
TO TELL MY PARENTS SOMEDAY SOON.
OH, I'M SURE
THEY'LL BE EXCITED.
WOULD YOU COME WITH ME...
NEXT WEEKEND?
OH, I DON'T THINK THAT--
PLEASE! THIS IS JUST TOO BIG.
I DON'T THINK I CAN
FACE THEM ALONE.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH. IT'LL BE GREAT.
REALLY.
THANKS SO MUCH BECAUSE
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'D DO
WITHOUT YOU.
NATASHA, COME ON.
THINGS HAVE BEEN SO BORING
WITHOUT YOU.
OH, STOP!
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK--
TOO LOW CUT?
HON, YOU SAW GREASE
LIKE 14 TIMES AS A KID.
HOW COULD YOU NOT HAVE GOTTEN
ITS MESSAGE?
SO, DID YOU SEE WHAT
TIMOTHY SENT ME?
I ASSUME THEY WEREN'T THIS
PATHETIC WHEN HE SENT THEM.
NO, THEY WERE BEAUTIFUL.
SO, HAVE YOU TALKED?
NO, HE LEFT A MESSAGE.
BUT HAVE YOU TALKED?
HE LEFT A MESSAGE.
UH-HUH.
DON'T "UH-HUH" ME.
YOU KNOW HE'S BUSY
AT THE HOSPITAL.
TOO BUSY
FOR A CONVERSATION?
YES, AND DON'T ACT LIKE
THAT'S SOMETHING WEIRD.
DOCTOR'S HAVE
INSANE SCHEDULES.
YOU'VE SEEN ER.
I GUESS, BUT I'M GLAD WE'RE
GOING OUT TONIGHT.
NEVER HURTS TO HAVE BACKUPS.
I DON'T NEED A BACKUP.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT YOU.
I'M TALKING ABOUT ME.
SERGE IS DRIVING ME CRAZY!
OH, GOD!
WHAT DID HE DO NOW?
COOKING, LEAVING ME CUTE NOTES,
GIVING ME BACK RUBS.
OH, FOR GOD SAKES,
DUMP THE MAN ALREADY!
[INDISTINCT TALKING]
YOU DO REALIZE MOJITOS ARE SO
5 MINUTES AGO.
WHAT?
IT'S TRUE. IT'S IN EW,
AND THE SHAW REPORT NEVER LIES.
YEAH, SO WHAT'S IN?
SOMETHING I CAN'T PRONOUNCE,
WHICH MAKES IT
PAINFULLY CLEAR WHERE
MY SOCIAL STANDING LIES.
OOH! DID YOU HEAR
DRISCOLL MEYER
IS SINGLE AGAIN?
OH, MY GOD. I WAS SO IN LOVE
WITH DRISCOLL MEYER.
I KNOW. SHOULD I HAVE HIM
CALL YOU?
UH, GIVEN THAT THE LOVE MIGHT
HAVE DIMINISHED
HAD WE EVER ACTUALLY SPOKEN,
I DON'T THINK SO.
HER WEDDING'S A WEEK
FROM TOMORROW.
I THINK I ACTUALLY MIGHT
BE SEEING SOMEONE.
OK, DON'T TAKE THIS
THE WRONG WAY,
BUT PART OF THE DEFINITION
OF SEEING SOMEONE
IS ACTUALLY SEEING THEM.
HE LEFT ME A MESSAGE.
HAVE YOU TALKED?!
WELL, HE'S BUSY
AT THE HOSPITAL.
MAN IF YOU WENT
THROUGH ALL THIS
AND ENDED UP GOING
TO THE WEDDING ALONE.
YOU WANT TO KNOW THE TRUTH?
IT'S NOT EVEN ABOUT
A DATE FOR THE WEDDING ANYMORE.
IT'S ABOUT THE GUY--
A PARTNER--YOU KNOW,
FOR MORE THAN JUST
ONE AFTERNOON.
I HAD THAT WITH MAX,
AND I THINK I'M READY
TO HAVE THAT AGAIN,
AND I'M HOPING
IT'S WITH TIMOTHY.
WELL, YOU SHOULD HAVE THAT,
JANE! I MEAN IT!
NO, 'CAUSE FOR ALL THE WAYS
A RELATIONSHIP
SOMETIMES IT TURNS OUT BETTER
THAN YOU EVER IMAGINED.
I'VE GOT TO BREAK UP
WITH SERGE.
EXCUSE ME, THE MOJITO'S NOT
WORKING FOR HER.
YEAH, CAN I GET
A COSMO INSTEAD?
YOU REALLY DON'T GET OUT,
DO YOU?
WHAT? I LIKE COSMOS.
THEY'RE PINK.
OK, I SAY WE GIVE HER
THIS ONE,
BUT THE DAY SHE SHOWS UP
IN A PASHMINA,
WE'RE WRITING HER OFF
AS MARRIED AND BEYOND HELP.
JANE, WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S TIMOTHY.
LET'S GO.
JANE!
EXCUSE ME.
JANE, PLEASE LET ME
TALK TO YOU. PLEASE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT UP
THE STREET.
I SWEAR I WASN'T LYING
ABOUT THINGS BEING CRAZY
AT THE HOSPITAL,
YOU KNOW.
I'M THERE ALL THE TIME.
I JUST FIGURE IT WOULD BE EASIER
FOR ME TO GET INVOLVED
WITH SOMEONE WHO WAS GOING
THROUGH THE SAME STUFF.
I'M JUST SO SORRY
ABOUT THE TIMING.
I-I NEVER WOULD HAVE--
YOU--YOU ARE
A GREAT GIRL.
YOU'LL FIND SOMEONE.
I PROMISE.
IT'S JUST NOT ME.
I'M SORRY.
[ANVIL CHORUS PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
COMING.
I WENT TO COSTCO YESTERDAY.
THEY HAD A FABULOUS SALE
ON SHAMPOO.
THIS ONE SMELLS
LIKE MANGO.
OH, WELL, MY GIANT
AND I WILL ENJOY THAT.
AND YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE
WHAT I FOUND
WHEN I WAS DOING MY ERRANDS--
BRIDESMAID SHOES.
THEY WEREN'T PICKED UP.
I'M SORRY, AUNT INA,
I'VE BEEN BUSY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK'S BEST
FOR BEING BUSY?
GETTING UP BEFORE 10:00 A.M.
ON A SATURDAY.
MAKE SURE THAT YOU BREAK
THEM IN BEFORE THE WEDDING.
WHAT I SUGGEST IS YOU WALK
UP AND DOWN YOUR HALLWAY
EVERY DAY IN
INCREASING AMOUNTS.
WHAT IS IT--A WEDDING
OR A MARATHON?
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
WHAT'S THAT?
DO YOU HAVE A CELLPHONE?
WHEN DID YOU GET A CELLPHONE?
I ASKED YOU IF
YOU HAD A CELLPHONE SO
I COULD REACH YOU,
AND YOU SAID YOU
DIDN'T HAVE A CELLPHONE!
PLEASE STOP SAYING
CELLPHONE.
HELLO.
HI, JANE.
THIS IS DRISCOLL MEYER.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU
REMEMBER ME.
OF COURSE I REMEMBER YOU.
IS THAT TIMOTHY?
WHY IS HE ASKING YOU
IF YOU REMEMBER HIM?
I KNOW I DON'T HAVE
OFFICIAL CLEARANCE TO CALL YOU,
BUT I HAVE AN EXTRA TICKET
TO HAIRSPRAY TONIGHT,
AND I WOULD LOVE IT
IF YOU COULD COME.
OH, I GUESS
WE COULD DO THAT.
HOW ABOUT WE MEET
AT THE THEATER AT 6:00?
WE CAN GRAB
A DRINK FIRST.
WELL, I HAVE TO BE IN QUEENS
ALL DAY, SO IS 7:00 OK?
7:00 IT IS.
SEE YOU THEN.
OK. THANKS.
THAT SOUNDED A LITTLE
AWKWARD.
IT SOUNDED NORMAL.
IF YOU'RE HAVING PROBLEMS,
ETHAN MILES IS STILL SINGLE.
ETHAN MILES?
HAVE YOU MENTIONED
HIM BEFORE?
HE DOESN'T SOUND
FAMILIAR.
NOBODY LIKES
A SARCASTIC GIRL.
DO I LOOK OK?
YOU LOOK GREAT.
OK. [SIGHS]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
HI, MOM.
JANE, IT'S SO NICE
TO SEE YOU.
MY GOODNESS, YOU LOOK JUST LIKE
YOUR MOTHER,
MAY SHE REST IN PEACE.
PLEASE, COME IN.
COME IN.
CAN I GET YOU ANYTHING?
SOME ICED TEA, PERHAPS?
MMM. NO THANKS.
WHERE'S DADDY?
HE HAD TO GO OUT
FOR A WHILE.
HE SHOULD BE BACK SOON.
SO, JANE, I UNDERSTAND YOUR
COUSIN DANA IS GETTING MARRIED.
YES, NEXT WEEK
AT THE CARLTON.
OH, THE CARLTON.
WELL, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT SHE DESERVES.
SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN
SUCH A NICE GIRL.
YEAH. WELL, I MEAN,
YOU MUST BE SO PROUD OF NATASHA.
SHE'S A TERRIFIC ACTRESS,
AND AS IT TURNS OUT,
A WONDERFUL WRITER, TOO.
WELL, I UNDERSTAND
YOU'RE THE EDITOR OF THE BOOK.
I'M SURE HAVING A GOOD EDITOR
IS CRUCIAL TO SUCCESS.
DADDY'S NOT COMING BACK,
IS HE?
I ASSUME HE'LL BE BACK
AT SOME POINT.
BUT NOT UNTIL I LEAVE,
RIGHT?
NATASHA, DON'T ACT LIKE
THIS IS YOUR FATHER'S FAULT.
YOU MADE YOUR CHOICES.
YOU HAVE TO LIVE
WITH THE CONSEQUENCES.
WELL, UM,
IT'S JUST THAT I HAVE
SOME EXCITING NEWS,
AND I HAD HOPED
TO TELL YOU BOTH.
WELL, WHATEVER IT IS,
I CAN TELL HIM.
OK, UM, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE GRANDPARENTS.
I'M PREGNANT.
DO YOU KNOW
WHO THE FATHER IS?
YES, I DO.
IT'S SAM.
OH, WELL, I DIDN'T WANT
TO ASSUME.
YOU NEVER KNOW WITH YOU.
[SOBBING] YOU KNOW WHAT,
I SHOULDN'T HAVE COME.
I KNOW WHAT A DISAPPOINTMENT
I AM TO YOU,
AND YOU CAN TELL DADDY
I'M SORRY FOR ANY INCONVENIENCE.
OK, LET'S GO.
HEY, THEY DIDN'T
HAVE DIET. SORRY.
WHATEVER.
NATASHA, I'M SORRY,
BUT YOUR PARENTS ARE WRONG.
IT'S CRAZY
THAT THEY CAN'T SEE
HOW MUCH
YOU'VE ACCOMPLISHED.
LIKE WHAT?
DROPPING OUT OF COLLEGE
TO BECOME AN ACTRESS,
GOING INTO REHAB,
HAVING A RIDICULOUS AFFAIR
AND THEN GOSSIPING ABOUT IT
IN THE TABLOIDS.
YEAH, BUT YOU'VE GOTTEN
THROUGH ALL THOSE THINGS.
YOU'VE TURNED EVERY PROBLEM
INTO A POSITIVE.
THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
NO, YOU'RE THE ONE
WITH THE IMPRESSIVE LIFE.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
JEALOUS OF YOU.
WHAT?
[LAUGHING] I MEAN IT.
YOU'VE ALWAYS KNOWN
HOW TO GET WHAT YOU WANT,
LIKE WHEN WE RAN
AGAINST EACH OTHER
YOU GAVE THIS GREAT SPEECH
ABOUT WHAT YOU
HOPED TO ACCOMPLISH,
HAD THOSE CUTE
LITTLE BUTTONS
MADE IN THE SHAPE
OF BAND-AIDS
THAT SAID "AVOID PAIN...
Both: VOTE FOR JANE."
[LAUGHING]
AND I WORE A HALTER TOP.
AND YOU WON.
BUT I SHOULDN'T HAVE.
YOU'VE GOT
GREAT FRIENDS,
AND A FAMILY
WHO LOVES YOU.
AND YOU'RE
AN EXECUTIVE EDITOR.
I MEAN, YOU'VE WORKED
REALLY HARD FOR THAT.
I ADMIRE THAT.
THANK YOU.
UM, IT'S NOT
ENTIRELY TRUE, THOUGH.
IT'S NOT?
NO.
I'M AN ASSISTANT EDITOR.
EXECUTIVE EDITOR
ISN'T EVEN A REAL TITLE.
WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL ME THIS BEFORE?
WELL, BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT
THE ONLY ONE
THAT'S SPENT A LONG TIME
THINKING SOME ELSE'S LIFE
WAS MORE IMPRESSIVE
THAN THEIR OWN.
HMM.
HUH.
HEY, YOU'RE SEEING HAIRSPRAY
TONIGHT. WE SHOULD GO.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
I'M GOOD HERE.
HEY, I HAVEN'T
SEEN YOU ALL DAY.
I'M GIVING THE FIRST
2 CHAPTERS
OF NATASHA'S BOOK
TO REMKE
AND I WANT THEM
TO BE PERFECT.
THAT'S WEIRD.
WHAT?
I NEVER HEARD YOU
CALL HER NATASHA.
HUH.
ALL RIGHT. WELL,
DON'T STAY TOO LATE.
YOU'VE GOT THE BACHELORETTE
PARTY, RIGHT?
YEAH.
TRY NOT TO LET DANA
GET TOO CRAZY.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'LL BE A PROBLEM.
OH, JANE.
I'M SORRY.
WELL, HI.
I'M GLAD YOU COULD SQUEEZE US
INTO YOUR BUSY SCHEDULE.
YEAH, I WAS TRYING
TO GET AHEAD
SO I DON'T HAVE TO WORK
THIS WEEKEND.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I'D
CERTAINLY HOPE
YOU WEREN'T THINKING
ABOUT WORK AT MY WEDDING.
YES. YES.
COME ON. GO HERE.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE YOUR TOES AND
YOUR FINGERS DONE, ALL RIGHT?
OH, GREAT.
OK.
ALL RIGHT, UH,
I BROUGHT MY OWN POLISH.
OH, WE'RE--WE'RE ALL
GETTING PRECIOUS PEACH
TO MATCH WITH
THE CHAMPAGNE DRESSES.
IT'S LIKE A BELLINI.
OK, I'LL WEAR PRECIOUS PEACH
ON MY FINGERNAILS.
WE'RE ALL GETTING IT
ON OUR TOES, TOO.
BUT WE'RE
WEARING PUMPS.
OUR TOES ARE
GONNA BE COVERED.
BUT WE'RE ALL GETTING PRECIOUS
PEACH ON OUR TOES, TOO!
JANE, PLEASE
DON'T BE SO DIFFICULT.
AM I CRAZY?
I MEAN HOW COULD IT
POSSIBLY MATTER
WHAT COLOR IS ON OUR TOES
IF THEY'RE COVERED?
HONEY, THIS IS
DANA'S WEDDING.
DANA WANTS PRECIOUS PEACH.
NOW WHEN YOU GET MARRIED,
YOU CAN DECIDE WHAT YOU WANT,
ALL RIGHT?
FINE.
SO, JANE, I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M FINALLY GONNA MEET
THE MYSTERIOUS
TIMOTHY ROMMELLY.
YEAH. THE THING IS,
HE'S ON CALL.
HE'S NOT COMING?
NO, I'M REALLY SORRY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME SOONER.
THIS CERTAINLY
WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED
IF YOU HAD CHOSEN ETHAN.
WHY WOULD YOU RSVP
FOR 2 PEOPLE
IF THERE WAS CHANCE
ONE OF THEM WOULDN'T MAKE IT.
THAT'S $225
WE CAN'T GET BACK!
I...TOLD YOU
AS SOON AS I FOUND OUT.
OH, REALLY?
WELL, I WOULD SAY THE CHANCES
WERE PRETTY GOOD
THAT "TIMOTHY" WASN'T EVER
GOING TO MAKE IT!
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU
JUST DIDN'T GO ALONE!
YOU KNOW, DANA,
THAT'S FUNNY.
OR SHOULD I SAY "FUNNY"
BECAUSE IT'S REALLY NOT.
JANE, I THINK YOU NEED
TO CALM DOWN HERE.
NO, I AM SO SICK OF THIS!
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE RIGHT!
TIMOTHY IS NOT ON CALL
OR MAYBE HE IS,
BUT I WOULDN'T KNOW BECAUSE,
ALTHOUGH HE IS NOT IMAGINARY,
HE IS ALSO NOT MY BOYFRIEND!
I PRETENDED HE WAS!
YOU KNOW, I SOMEHOW LET MYSELF
BE CONVINCED
THAT A WOMAN IS NOT NORMAL
UNLESS SHE HAS A BOYFRIEND,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM NORMAL!
AT LEAST I AM
THE SAME AMOUNT OF NORMAL
AS I WOULD BE WITH A BOYFRIEND,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT--
[SOBBING]
THE POINT IS IT'S NOT EVEN
ABOUT THE BOYFRIEND!
I HAVE A REALLY GOOD LIFE!
I HAVE A LIFE THAT IS
FULL OF MORE MEANINGFUL THINGS
THAN DEPLETING THE WORLD
OF THE COLOR PRECIOUS PEACH!
AND I'M NOT GONNA LET ANYONE
MAKE LESS OF MY LIFE
BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE
A BOYFRIEND!
WELL, NO WONDER SHE DOESN'T
HAVE A BOYFRIEND!
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
I GAVE REMKE THE PARTIALS
FOR NATASHA'S BOOK,
I NEED TO THINK
ABOUT ANYTHING ELSE.
DRISCOLL MEYER
IS BADMOUTHING YOU
ALL OVER TOWN.
WHAT? I CALLED 20 DIFFERENT
MEYERS IN MANHATTAN.
IS IT MY FAULT
HE'S NOT LISTED?
YEAH, WELL, APPARENTLY,
HE WENT TO HAIRSPRAY ALONE.
HARVEY FIERSTEIN HIT ON HIM
AFTER THE SHOW.
OHH! YIKES! TELL HIM
I'LL PAY FOR HIS THERAPY.
WILLIAM WOULD LIKE TO SEE YOU
IN THE CONFERENCE ROOM...NOW.
OK, I HAVE TO GO.
TELL ME NOT TO THROW UP.
EW!
[SIGHS]
HEY. WHO'S
GETTING MARRIED NOW?
THANK YOU ALL FOR COMING.
I KNOW YOU HAVE WORK TO DO
AND IF YOU DON'T,
THEN SEE ME AFTERWARDS
I HATE WHEN HE
TRIES TO BE FUNNY.
I HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT
TO MAKE.
EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY,
JANE GRANT IS BEING PROMOTED
TO EDITOR.
UH, DON'T YOU MEAN
ASSOCIATE EDITOR?
SHE'S BEEN PROMOTED
FOR 5 SECONDS,
ALREADY SHE'S QUESTIONING
THE BOSS.
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN VERY LOYAL
TO BLUSH PUBLISHING.
NOT ONLY DID YOU STAY
IN AN ASSISTANT POSITION
A LOT LONGER THAN YOU
PROBABLY SHOULD HAVE,
YOU'RE DOING A JOB
ON THE NUTLEY AUTOBIOGRAPHY.
CONGRATULATIONS, JANE!
CONGRATULATIONS!
OOH! GOOD JOB!
YOU'RE SO BUYING DINNER
THE NEXT TIME WE GO OUT.
IT'S A DEAL.
GOOD JOB, JANE!
OH, THANK YOU.
I WANT YOUR OFFICE
WHEN YOU MOVE.
LOOK WHAT YOU DID!
I'M SO INCREDIBLY PROUD OF YOU!
THANKS, YEAH, IT WAS
A LONG TIME COMING.
YOU KNOW NO ONE DESERVES THIS
MORE THAN YOU DO.
YEAH, I KNOW.
THANKS.
CHEERS.
YES!
OF COURSE
I TRIED ON THE SHOES.
WHY, DO YOU THINK I'M GONNA
SPEND ALL DAY
IN A BRAND NEW PAIR OF SHOES?
I MEAN, I'M NOT STUPID!
GOOD, I'M GLAD YOU DID
SOMETHING RIGHT
WITH THIS WEDDING.
LISTEN, AUNT INA,
I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT THE THING AT THE SPA.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
I CALLED DANA,
I APOLOGIZED,
AND WE'RE GOOD.
I SWEAR NOTHING LIKE THAT
IS GONNA HAPPEN TODAY
AT THE WEDDING.
IT'S GONNA BE BEAUTIFUL.
THANK YOU, HONEY.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
I'LL SEE YOU SOON. OK.
OHH!
OUCH!
OW!
OHH! OUCH!
OH! I WAS JUST
BREAKING IN MY SHOES.
WE'VE LIVED NEXT DOOR
TO EACH OTHER FOREVER
AND WE'VE NEVER
ACTUALLY MET.
I'M JANE.
ARCHIBALD.
ARCHI--WOW!
[LAUGHING]
WHAT?
NOTHING.
IT'S JUST NOT A NAME
YOU HEAR A LOT.
IT'S NICE, THOUGH.
GOOD FOR YOU.
OHH!
[SIGHS]
AHH! YES!
OW!
[SIGHS]
OHH.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
WHO IS IT?
IT'S US.
IT'S OPEN.
HEY!
WE FIGURED YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE TIME TO MEET US!
YOU GUYS ROCK!
YOU KNOW, WE'D HAVE
ROCKED MORE
IF ELOISE HADN'T EATEN
YOUR SCONE.
IT WAS REALLY GOOD.
WE GOT THIS FOR YOU.
OH, WHAT'S THIS?
WELL, WE FIGURED DANA GETS
OLD, NEW, BORROWED AND BLUE,
SO THE LEAST WE COULD DO
WAS GET YOU SOMETHING
TO GET YOU THROUGH THE DAY.
A FLASK?
NOT JUST A FLASK,
A CHAMPAGNE-COLORED FLASK.
'CAUSE IF IT WASN'T
COLOR-COORDINATED,
WHAT WONDERFUL, ENABLING FRIENDS
I HAVE.
JUST DON'T HIT ON
YOUR GROOMSMAN.
[LAUGHING]
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THE WEDDING PARTY
IS THE ONLY REASON
TO BE A BRIDESMAID.
I'M WALKING LARRY'S GRANDFATHER
DOWN THE AISLE,
I THINK I CAN RESIST.
SHE COULDN'T EVEN
GIVE YOU A HOT GROOMSMAN!
SHE'S SO SELFISH!
OK, HERE'S WHAT YOU'RE
GONNA DO--
EVERY TIME DANA GOES TO TAKE
A BITE OF HER DINNER TONIGHT,
YOU'RE GONNA START THAT ANNOYING
GLASS TAPPING THING
SO SHE AND LARRY HAVE TO KISS
AND SHE ENDS UP STARVING.
OH, EVIL DISGUISED
AS ROMANTIC--I LIKE IT.
SO, SERIOUSLY, ARE YOU
GONNA BE OK?
YEAH, WELL,
AS LONG AS MY DRESS
IS LONG ENOUGH
TO COVER THE SNEAKERS
I'LL BE WEARING, I'M GOOD.
YOU KNOW, YOU'LL PROBABLY
HAVE MORE FUN ALONE, ANYWAY.
NOT JUST
WITH THE WEDDING,
IN LIFE IN GENERAL.
THAT'S TRUE.
YOU KNOW,
IT IS KIND OF A BURDEN
TO HAVE TO THINK ABOUT SOMEONE
ELSE'S FEELINGS ALL THE TIME.
ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY'RE
AS SENSITIVE AS JEFF IS.
HE CALLS IT ALLERGIES,
BUT I KNOW HE CRIES.
OH, SERGE ISN'T
ANY BETTER.
JUST TO COME OVER HERE
THIS MORNING,
I HAD TO SNEAK THE DOG
INTO THE BED
SO HE WOULDN'T NOTICE
I WAS GONE.
YOU DON'T HAVE A DOG.
WHICH WILL BE YET
ANOTHER THING TO EXPLAIN
IF HE WAKES UP EARLY.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
OH, WHO'S THAT?
PROBABLY THE PIZZA.
WE ORDERED DOMINO'S.
IT'S 8:00 IN THE MORNING.
YEAH, BUT THE DELIVERY GUY
COULD BE CUTE.
CONSIDER IT A HAIL MARY.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
IT GIVES ME GREAT PLEASURE
TO WELCOME
FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME
IN PUBLIC,
MR. AND MRS. LARRY FISHKILL.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ TO BE LOVED BY ANYONE ♪
♪ IT'S NOT UNUSUAL ♪
♪ TO HAVE FUN WITH ANYONE ♪
♪ BUT WHEN I SEE YOU
HANGING ABOUT WITH ANYONE ♪
♪ IT'S NOT UNUSUAL
TO SEE ME CRY ♪
♪ I WANT TO DIE ♪
CONGRATULATIONS.
♪ IT'S NOT UNUSUAL
TO GO OUT AT ANY TIME ♪
♪ BUT WHEN I SEE YOU
OUT AND ABOUT ♪
♪ IT'S SUCH A CRIME ♪
♪ IF YOU SHOULD EVER WANT
TO BE LOVED BY ANYONE ♪
♪ IT'S NOT UNUSUAL,
IT HAPPENS EVERY DAY ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHAT YOU SAY ♪
♪ YOU'LL FIND IT HAPPENS
ALL THE TIME... ♪
HI!
HI.
HEY!
IS THIS YOUR TABLE TOO?
YEAH, LUCKY NUMBER 17.
THANK GOD!
I HATE MAKING HOURS
OF ENDLESS SMALL TALK
WITH PEOPLE I DON'T KNOW.
YEAH, I KNOW.
HOW MANY TIMES CAN YOU
HEAR A PERSON ASK,
"HEY, SO HOW DO YOU
KNOW DANA"?
YEAH.
SO, WHERE'S SAM?
HE BROKE UP WITH ME.
WHAT? WHEN?
REMEMBER THAT DAY
I WENT TO YOUR APARTMENT?
IT WAS THE NIGHT
BEFORE THAT.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
NO, THINGS HAD BEEN
NOT SO GREAT FOR A WHILE,
AND I GUESS HAVING
A BABY FORCED US TO
MAKE SOME DECISIONS.
WELL, I THOUGHT YOU SAID
HE WAS HAPPY ABOUT IT.
YEAH, I LIED. SORRY.
WELL, HOW ARE YOU
HOLDING UP?
OK.
YOU KNOW, I'M JUST TRYING
TO STAY CALM
AND TAKE EVERYTHING
A DAY AT A TIME.
WOW! THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
YEAH, OK. I LIED AGAIN.
I AM SCARED TO DEATH.
WELL, THE FACT THAT
YOU CAN ADMIT THAT
SAYS THAT YOU HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO GO THROUGH WITH THIS.
I MEAN IT.
THANKS.
WHERE'S TIMOTHY?
YEAH, HE'S FOOLING AROUND
WITH SOMEONE ELSE.
WHAT?!
YEAH, A LONG, STUPID STORY,
BUT, UH, I'M FLYING SOLO.
WELL, WE MAKE A FINE PAIR.
MM-HMM.
YEAH, I HOPE YOU'RE PREPARED
TO EAT $450 WORTH OF SALMON
OR ELSE DANA'S GONNA
PITCH A FIT.
[GLASS CLINKING]
EVERYONE, EVERYONE,
THE BRIDE AND GROOM
WOULD LIKE YOUR ATTENTION.
I'M GONNA GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
AGAIN?
YEAH, I'M PREGNANT.
APPARENTLY IT'S WHAT WE DO.
OK, IF THIS IS A PLOY
TO GET OUT OF THE BOUQUET TOSS,
YOU'RE IN BIG TROUBLE.
OH, NO, BABY, JUST STOP,
DROP, AND ROLL.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
Larry: I KNOW IT'S SOMEWHAT
UNTRADITIONAL
FOR THE GROOM
TO MAKE THE TOAST,
BUT IT'S MY WEDDING,
I'LL DO WHAT I WANT.
TODAY'S A DAY
FOR CELEBRATION,
AND AFTER MEETING DANA,
YOU CAN UNDERSTAND MY ELATION.
THE DAY SHE AGREED
TO BE MY WIFE
IS ONE THAT I'LL TREASURE
ALL MY LIFE,
AND THOUGH TIMES
CAN GET TOUGH,
I KNOW THAT OUR LOVE
WILL BE ENOUGH.
HERE'S TO EMBARKING
ON AN AMAZING RIDE
WITH MY FRIEND,
MY SOUL MATE,
MY BEAUTIFUL BRIDE.
TO DANA.
All: TO DANA.
AM I THE LUCKIEST GIRL
IN THE WORLD OR WHAT?
SINCE TODAY
IS A CELEBRATION OF LOVE,
MY HUSBAND, LARRY, AND I
WOULD LIKE TO INVITE
ALL THE COUPLES
TO COME OUT
AND SHARE A SPECIAL DANCE.
♪ THERE'S
A MOON WIND BLOWING ♪
♪ AND IT FEELS
LIKE IRELAND ♪
♪ AND IT LIGHTS
YOUR EYES TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND MY GREATEST BLESSING ♪
♪ IS JUST
TO SEE YOU SMILING ♪
♪ AND WHY IS IT ME ♪
♪ WHO GETS
TO FEEL SO RIGHT? ♪
♪ IT COULDN'T GET
MUCH BETTER ♪
♪ GET MUCH BETTER ♪
♪ THAN RIGHT THIS MINUTE ♪
♪ THERE'S PRECIOUS MOMENTS ♪
♪ IN OUR LIVES ♪
♪ OOH ♪
♪ ALL THIS MAGIC MOONIGHT ♪
♪ ON THIS STARRY EVENING ♪
♪ NEVER, EVER BE
A BETTER NIGHT ♪
♪ THERE'S A TIMELESS MAGIC ♪
♪ AND IT MADE US TREASURE ♪
♪ THERE'S A MOON
IN YOUR GREEN EYES ♪
♪ AND THE WIND
SING LOW... ♪
HI.
I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU REMEMBER ME,
BUT WE MET WHEN YOU STARTED
YOUR WORLDWIDE CAMPAIGN
AGAINST WEDDING REGISTRIES.
OH, RIGHT.
OH, MY GOD!
HOW COULD I FORGET?
I'VE ONLY SEEN YOU LIKE
A GAZILLION TIMES.
I'M JUST A LITTLE SURPRISED
TO SEE YOU HERE.
OH, WELL, I'M NOT SURPRISED
TO SEE YOU.
YOU'RE NOT?
I ACTUALLY FIND MYSELF
LOOKING FOR YOU
EVERY TIME I'M AT ONE.
WELL, THEN THAT'S SWEET
AND SLIGHTLY STALKERISH.
OH, OK. I BETTER GET
TO MY POINT THEN BEFORE
I SCARE YOU OFF.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO DANCE?
WELL, ARE WE ALLOWED?
WELL, TECHNICALLY
WE'RE NOT A COUPLE,
BUT I CAN'T TAKE
THE HUMILIATION ANYMORE.
OH, WELL, I WON'T TELL
IF YOU DON'T.
DEAL.
[LAUGHTER]
♪ I COULD SEE
THE TRUST GROW IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ NOW WE SHARE
A PROMISE ♪
♪ AND WE KNOW
THE MEANING ♪
♪ WE WILL HAVE
THESE MEMORIES ♪
♪ FOR THE REST
OF OUR LIVES ♪
♪ DOESN'T GET MUCH BETTER ♪
♪ GET MUCH BETTER ♪
♪ THAN RIGHT THIS-- ♪
[NEW SONG BEGINS]
♪ BEAT OF, THE BEAT
OF MY HEART ♪
♪ OOH, OOH ♪
♪ CAN YOU FEEL THE HEAT? ♪
♪ CAN YOU FEEL THE BEAT?
CAN YOU FEEL THE HEAT? ♪
♪ CAN YOU FEEL THE HEAT
OF THE BEAT OF MY HEART? ♪
♪ OOH, OOH ♪
♪ CAN YOU FEEL THE HEAT? ♪
♪ CAN YOU FEEL THE BEAT?
CAN YOU FEEL THE HEAT? ♪
♪ CAN YOU FEEL THE HEAT
OF THE BEAT OF MY HEART? ♪
♪ CAN YOU FEEL
THE BEAT... ♪
♪ OH, SHANDA ♪
♪ WE'LL LET OUR HEARTS
SAIL AWAY ♪
♪ RIDE THE WIND AND WAVES ♪
♪ MAKE LOVE
IN MOONLIGHT, BABE ♪
♪ IN THE OCEAN OF LOVE ♪
♪ THE OCEAN OF LOVE ♪
♪ DO YOU FEEL IT? ♪E ♪
OK,
I THINK I NEED A TIMEOUT.
OH, THANK GOD!
I DIDN'T KNOW
HOW MUCH LONGER
I COULD WILL MYSELF
NOT TO SWEAT!
CAN I GET YOU A GLASS
OF WATER?
AND INSTEAD OF WATER MAKE IT
VODKA, DRY UP WITH A TWIST.
WHOA! ALL RIGHT.
YOU GOT IT!
WHAT?
SEE, NOW THIS IS
THE PROBLEM
WITH HAVING
PRETTY FRIENDS,
THEY ALWAYS GET THE GUY.
OH, STOP IT!
HE'S CUTE.
YEAH, HE IS.
OK, WELL,
I'LL LEAVE YOU 2 ALONE.
NO, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO DO THAT!
NATASHA!
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THIS MAY BE MY LAST SHOT
AT SINGLE GUYS
BEFORE I START SHOWING.
HI. OHH!
I'M JUST SO HAPPY!
WELL, YOU SHOULD.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL WEDDING.
EVERYTHING--
OH, NO, NO, NO!
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT THAT.
I'M TALKING ABOUT ETHAN.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
ETHAN MILES--THE YOUNG MAN
YOU'VE BEEN DANCING WITH.
WHAT?
SEE, NOW WHAT DOES THIS
TEACH YOU, YOUNG LADY?
YOU SHOULD ALWAYS LISTEN
TO YOUR AUNT.
OH, IT'S JUST SO GREAT,
JANE!
OH, IT'S JUST...
OK, ONE MARTINI-FLAVORED
GLASS OF WATER.
THANK YOU.
[LAUGHING]
AND YOU'RE LAUGHING.
YEAH. IT'S A LONG STORY.
RIGHT--
WHICH YOU'LL TELL ME SOMEDAY.
DEFINITELY, BUT WE CANNOT
KEEP IGNORING THE FACT
THAT THERE IS OLD SCHOOL PUNK
PLAYING IN THE CARLTON.
NOW THROW IN SOME LOCUSTS
AND THAT'S A SIGN
OF THE APOCALYPSE, RIGHT?
LET'S DO IT!
COME ON!
YEAH!
♪ YOU CAUSE A SCENE
TO PROVE YOU'RE WILD ♪
♪ BUT YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS ♪
♪ SO IT COMES OFF AS MILD ♪
♪ AND EVERYTHING YOU SAID
IS SPOON-FED ♪
♪ AND EVERYTHING YOU'VE READ
IS EDITED ♪
♪ YOU'RE AT THE TOP,
YOU'RE AT THE TOP ♪
♪ OF MY HIT LIST ♪
♪ YOU'RE AT THE TOP,
YOU'RE AT THE TOP ♪
♪ OF MY HIT LIST... ♪
SO, I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
THAT BY WRITING THIS BOOK,
I'M ONCE AGAIN...
ONE OF THE MOST FAMOUS ACTORS
IN SHOW BUSINESS,
ONLY THIS TIME,
I'M ACTUALLY ENJOYING IT.
WHOA!
FIN!
FIN?
IT DOESN'T ACTUALLY SAY FIN,
DOES IT?
YES, NATASHA THOUGHT
IT SOUNDED EUROPEAN.
SO DOES NOT SHOWERING, THAT
DOESN'T MAKE IT A GOOD IDEA.
[LAUGHING]
OH, SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OH, NO! YOU PAUSED!
I DIDN'T PAUSE.
YOU DID!
NOW WHATEVER YOU SAY
I KNOW ISN'T GONNA BE
YOUR FIRST THOUGHT.
IT'S GONNA BE SOMETHING
YOU CAREFULLY CRAFTED.
WHAT--
DURING THAT HALF-SECOND PAUSE?
YEAH, YOU WORK FAST.
YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT I THINK?
YES.
I THINK IT'S GOOD.
YEAH?
YEAH, REALLY GOOD.
THANKS.
SO GOOD, IN FACT,
MY MANHOOD MAY BE
A LITTLE THREATENED HERE.
OH, THAT'S BAD.
I KNOW.
WHEN I MET YOU,
I THOUGHT I WAS JUST GETTING
A HOT CHICK.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN DEAL
WITH YOU BEING TALENTED
AND SMART, TOO.
WELL, IF YOU WANT,
I COULD GO BLOND
AND START TALKING
LIKE A LOCAL ANCHORWOMAN.
NOW THAT'D BE A START.
MAYBE YOU COULD GET A JOB
IN A FOOD COURT
TO REALLY SELL IT.
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU LET ME
ROW A WHILE.
YEAH.
HEY, WE SHOULD PROBABLY
HEAD BACK SOON.
THE HOUR'S ALMOST UP.
OH, NO!
OH, WELL, NOW
WHAT DO WE DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN YOU CAN'T ROW
WITH ONE OAR.
NO, YOU CAN'T.
I GUESS YOU'RE STUCK
WITH ME.
BUMMER.
Amanda: OH, MY GOD!
SHE USED THE OAR TRICK!
Eloise: LOOKS LIKE THIS ONE'S
A KEEPER.
NAH, THERE'S STILL
PLENTY OF TIME
TO FIND OUT HE'S
AN AX-MURDERER WHO LITTERS.
WELL, SHE CAN ALWAYS
HAVE SERGE.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE
BY HALLMARK CHANNEL
AND FRIENDS OF NCI
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--